Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never
The unexpected
Strange and unusual step inside the flow the circus of shadows its psyches show
Terrible trolls in the dark take their stand, but angels are dancing torchlight in
Psyche's show, terrible trolls in the dark take their stand
The angels are dancing, torchlight in hand
Let's start the show
Come to see
Pins, a show in the panel verse where tarot, truth and raw conversation meet
We explore boldly, we disagree intelligently and we protect the circle
Here's how we roll.
House rules.
Debate ideas.
Not people.
No doxing.
Slander.
Hate.
Or threats.
Ever.
Bring receipts, claims need sources or timestamps, no rumour relays, signal discipline, mix muted
and less called, no spam, no derail, the mods are the guardians, warning time out, ban,
no negotiations mid-show.
This is Psyche's channel, Psyche's Rules.
He keeps it safe, sharp and on topic.
Use common sense and be respectful to everyone and you will be fine.
Contribute or be entertained.
Welcome, if you're here to sow chaos.
Hang out, there's a place for you here too.
Now welcome your host, Psyche Sia,
storyteller and your host.
E-Truth, first shadow, second.
Let's get into it.
She laughs and riddles, she whispers and flames
Play his hide and seek with the shadows of name
turns every
What's up, guys? I'm here.
Where's my glasses?
Well, what's up with these things?
They're really nerdy glasses, okay.
I don't see my other ones. Hey, what's up, guys?
Hey, He-Man, what's up? He-Man, Sam-Man.
Is that the real Sam-Man? I'm not sure.
How'd you like, do you like this stuff?
bunch of stuff, but I have anything else, I don't know if I can find the last thing I had.
It's really good, or I'll find it later.
My desktop, no.
I also put Shorts up on there, take one more thing.
Documents.
Yeah, I'm still learning, really, but I'm trying my best.
Uh, and I don't see the, uh, whatever I was looking for.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, hold on.
Here.
Uh, oh, maybe one more thing.
Okay.
So, what's up guys?
Hey, man.
I'm over here.
You're laying on my green screen
Green screen fell down and you're laying on it like a oh, it's a real salmon. Okay, cool
Well, I
Suppose I will mod you because I need to make sure that I know the real one I
Don't like imposters. Let me see if I can find what I was gonna show you. Oh, where is it?
I lost it, I lost it, I lost it, okay, but it's okay.
Okay, I'm gonna log into it a little bit.
Thank you for being here, everybody.
Oh, by your team, Beta, oh no.
Well, you know what, I still love Beta, but it's like,
you know.
Ah, I don't know how things get so messed up. I don't know. She doesn't remember what she said.
I can't talk about her since she says I'm obsessed with throwing stuff. I'm just responding to what she said.
I think people are interested, but I hopefully will make up, but I just hope that it was like some kind of like
crazy misunderstanding. I don't know. I don't know.
Capable of being being I don't think
I've been around a lot of people that like you know, I'll give it time
You know people some people say stuff and it's like they don't mean it. I don't you know
I remember when I got drunk I would like wake up the next day and like
They're really probably screenshots of me or like
Be like what happened like the review mad at me, and then they get like these people emailing me screenshots, and I would
Say it's a sometimes terrible things
That I don't remember sometimes hey, yeah, hey Samantha and so I
Don't know I don't I don't have to be on teams and like what one fight I like I really do like to get along and like
Heal things big things. I don't know
It's screwed up
the pages
He just probably bad at me who else
Christine Christine mad I
Haven't do anything to her. I love Christine Christine first of all
She hasn't been here for like weeks. No, she's like but she's been working like but she hasn't been here for weeks or anything
So I already feel like she's like, you know, abandoned me, but then she goes back to yell at me.
I was trying to get her attention. I was like trying to, I don't know, I do sometimes like, you know, try to get people's attention.
Well, let's say I don't understand the peaking side there. I think I would have just stayed over here like she could say
She finally said don't come from a show. I haven't been to her show since she said she's the one down on her show. I
Would like I would respect that totally, you know, it's like
right
And I don't know
Hope we'd make up again, but a little crazy
Anyway, so happy happy Wednesday, though
You know, I had a
You see oh, thank you 200,000 views guys. I think yeah, that might even they know that is like
From I think I might I mean I might have more I don't know if that's counting like the ones I deleted because if it's like
Counting the ones that are needed. I probably have like almost half a million views. I've probably deleted a lot of stuff, but
Still but once they had a million views like a million I mean the million people of
I'm one fifth the way there, right and it's going faster and faster. I think by the end of this year
Maybe a million years that'd be so cool a million views
That's a lot of fucking views like a million. Wow
Yeah, I know
And then she's like, oh, she doesn't want me like calling her early talk or I don't know I can't do anything, right?
so I was like
I'll leave it alone, but I hate fighting.
Hi, Charisma!
So, yeah, hey Electro, what's up?
Yeah, so I've been working with this software called,
what's it called?
It's a really good software.
It's called CAPCUT, C-A-P-C-U-T.
Okay, and I'll show you like another one of the videos. I made out of it
I'll show you on YouTube because my own videos are all messing up. Okay, so
this one is
The Venus in Sagittarius one
Or Venus in the 12th house, but it's also the Venus in Sagittarius song
Let's see how it turned out. I know it's like I had to slow it slow them down
I'm still learning how to edit right and stuff.
Let me see, videos, okay, yeah, this is it.
See how you like this one, I'll be right back.
of silence where secrets are kept. Venus hides softly where dreams intersect. In the
12th house of fire, shadows ignite. Sagittarius aims through the dark toward
the light. You love like a pilgrim on paths never known. Seeking the sacred where wild
Your heart is a compass, it points past the veil
Total of that is boundless, a myth on the trail
Hidden arrows of love, they fly unseen
Through the caverns of spirit, through the infinite dream
Every secret devotion, every prayer to the skies
Venus in the twelfth
Centaur rides quiet through jungles of night
Hunting for freedom for truth dressed in light
Your love is a lantern for souls that are lost
You pay for your beauty with karmic cost
they fly unseen through the caverns of spirit through the infinite dream every secret devotion
So I think that yeah, so I'll get better at making these but
Yeah, I'll get better at making them, but I'm gonna go through like and do like a lot of songs about my placements
And then I'll go also other people's placements
I should get like a big library of like
really informative full videos with like music and the media and
I think I'll be really cool though
Hey, Electra! How's everyone doing today?
Oh, gosh.
Here are the ambulances, that's like...
It's a little loud here.
I don't know, so...
Yeah, I don't know, but I have more surprises for you.
Like, I have some...
I don't know if I should, like, you know, wait to tell you about it,
but I'll just say...
I have a free, something really cool, it's going to be free, coming out, and oh, thank
you Electra, yeah, I think I'm getting better, I want to say one more thing, I actually made
a cap recording video, I don't know if there's a cap recording here, but it's a short, and
Okay, let's see, video shorts, okay.
Okay, I did play up ten new shorts, too, but here's the amazing capricorn, okay, here we go.
Capricorn. The mountain goat who does not stop until the summit is theirs.
They move with patience. With an unshakable focus, scaling obstacles that others would not even attempt to climb.
Ruled by Saturn, the planet of discipline and destiny. Capricorns are forged in the crucible of hard lessons.
Each trial sharpens their will. Each setback becomes a stepping stone, where others falter, they ascend higher.
They don't just chase dreams. They build them stone by stone, until the peak itself bows to their persistence.
none climbs higher, none endures longer, and none achieves more than the indomitable Capricorn.
Capricorn, when the going gets tough, it's you who get going. You are the embodiment of resilience,
the personification of hard work and success. Your star sign may not have all the answers,
but it has the courage to face the unknown, the strength to overcome any obstacle,
and the wisdom to know that the only limit is the one you set for yourself.
So keep climbing, Capricorn. The world is yours for the taking. This is Capricorn,
Okay, hold on. So, Tracy. Hold on a second. Tracy. So, yeah, we're all doing good. It's
a blogger last night. So, again, blogger seems to be heavy. I'll show you what happened
to blogger last week, Tracy. I mean, you can get kind of an idea of what's going on, because
I'm abusive to people like you know Alex and anybody that like likes me for some reason
I don't know Alex Alex knows what's going on. It's like but he
He's a jealous or I don't know what's going on. He's like he doesn't like me or something, but you see
I think that's a quick kick
Yeah, this is one quick kick and
I think it's gonna be here.
Where is it?
Shit.
I haven't really looked at the people.
I saw it recently, let me see.
Berry, salmon, pig-times.
Oh yeah, well, here he is throwing.
I don't see it now.
Shit, let me see.
He, I mean, he threw up last week, let's see.
I forgot what it was on.
Oh yeah, here it is, okay.
It's untrue.
Okay, so Tracy, watch this, this will explain some stuff.
You know Alex, right?
Okay, here we go.
I got a whole lot of niggas using nobody
You ain't got nobody
See niggas that know about it
Like the niggas know about me
People on the scene
That complainin' old screens
Check the floor and low it be
I'm so fresh and something clean
Stuff them pants on my jeans
Slap them dirty things
Pull the trigger, let it sink
Dingo, smoke or rush or creep
I got money billin'
I get so high, I can't breathe, like a bum bitch, I'm a king.
We didn't need your kind out here in my throat.
I actually have like a pretty smart intellect in my brain.
Dude, is that Alexander Meyers?
You like you could have done better.
We had we literally had high hopes for you, Alexander Meyers.
We literally had high hopes for Alexander Meyers before she fell so far off course.
I don't know about a PDF thing, I don't know, I don't know about that, but I don't know about that chat.
I used to, hey, hey, I'll tell you this, Alex has a good, like, streaming voice.
She has a good voice to, like, talk to people.
She's, she's, unlike me, unlike me, she's organized and she's able to, like,
You know kind of have a layout in her head of how she wants to do her stream. That's not me. That's not how I do my shit
Unfortunately, I wish I did
That's not me at all, you know
Blazing Alex if anything chat, it's me setting a trap for Alex and I think she just fell for a guess
And chat listen, I liked Alex so much. I I literally pushed for Alex so hard
You know, but now it's like she fell into my trap. Yes, you did Alex
Alex the way that you're I swear to God Alex the way Alex Alex Alex the way that you're clinging to psych right now
Now what are we upon right now chat? Let's take heed. Let's take heed of the season that we were upon us
We are in fall time almost and what happens in fall all of the all of the arachnids come out
Don't think all the spiders come out. Don't they Alex?
Alex Alex has arachnid tendencies
You love psych by the way Alex
Alex dude, I've studied your feeding habits
Psych is like about six and a quarter months away from being totally demolished by you
Fucking figured out Alex
She's Christ, Alex.
Figure it out, Alex.
Yo, Chad, I wouldn't be saying bullshit like this.
It's not bullshit.
Alex has a rhythm and a flow.
She go and turn a fucking dyke bitch into a hoe.
Not a no, but Alex, I know what you're doing, okay?
You're friends with Psych right now.
You're getting him comfortable.
You're getting him docile.
You're letting him suck from your nectar
of your fucking Venus fly trap.
And you're letting him get intoxicated and and and roam about and right
You're disgusting. You're disgusting, Alex
I swear to goodness gracious Alex, I literally was trying to be a friend Alex chat
I don't know what Alex is gonna say. I haven't scrolled up yet. I was trying to be this woman's friend
Yeah, you'll be spider-girl. Okay, whatever. I don't know dude Alex. I'm just saying
I've seen a couple people take L's lately like as far as like on the stream of I don't know
I've taken L's myself job
Ask me who a child I'll tell you who right away. I'll tell you who right away. I'll tell you I'll tell you who in my opinion
I was like, oh
You know this person they're on the streams a lot, and they're like retarded and shit, but they're here. I
Literally just scrolled up on everybody's name, and I didn't read anything you guys said so I'm so sorry. I'm so fucking apologetic
but
This person Alexander Myers
This person Alexander Myers is somebody
Who
I don't know I don't know dude shout to you Alex, but you know your game is weak lately. Okay, so figure it out
Sometimes my feelings can teeter and totter, you know what I mean you film the job
You feel me and then and then sometimes there's times where like I really try to have gratitude
I try to have gratitude in certain things that are very might be simple might be simple might be Monday
Something tonight to where someone had I think I'm hoping it was only alcohol might have been more blogger
Hmm because you brought psyche awakens into the equation
Blogger had a temper tantrum
What happened
I'll recap it. I'll recap it. That way you know give me give me a summary before because I definitely want to watch the recap
You have the source of it not on purpose not only okay. Just tell me who was he fucking raging out of me first me
Well, you know bloggers always had this like he just thinks like really not so highly of blogger
And you know blogger by like vice versa. They just do not mesh
I thought they look alike and they had a lot in common, but they don't like each other at all
They do
Blogger was probably drunk. He's fucking rage at me about stupid fucking shit
But if you align yourself with you know anybody that he doesn't agree with he'll have a little he's just all like accent
caricature I
like blogger
Please don't
Don't like him. Okay. No, don't be mad at me. Why would it be mad at you? I don't know
Oh my god
You're just I thought I was sensitive. We're both sensitive. I would never be mad at you. I don't I don't like I
Am being overly sensitive. I don't like a lot like I want there to be some sort of
Just
Peace when it comes to whatever but I understand that there is a certain level of adrenaline that
Some of you might like when it comes to the enter so
Certain things that me and you are not aware of because we're not spending time in this board, you know
That's what it is
Question and I'm just asking a woman a woman just to make sure you're okay. Is anyone trying to extort you?
No, because I really don't know what they could extort me for
Is anyone saying or presenting something in a way to where if you're not kind to them, they're going to do something that you may not want them to do when it comes to your reputation.
No, my reputation is already fucked up and nobody can ever like do anything or like I would make it clear
I'd be like this fucking person is trying to fucking do this this and not to me fucking hell. No, no
Can I ask you and you don't have to you don't have to say it, but you have someone specific in mind?
I do I won't say okay if you were to listen to a recent live that I did earlier a few hours ago on my
And I hope you don't mind me saying the channel beta IP to with the info
Of course. No, I want your yeah, I mean, I don't want some people that are dirty over there
I'm a little worried when it comes because beta is very nice
And I know how people can be and I know that beta is very diplomatic and very smart and I think that she can get herself out of anything or situation, but the reason I just asked the question was because I wanted to know how she felt when she told me how she feels.
So it's in my head.
But I do have a certain turn for certain people, not only streamers, but chatters or anyone in this in these communities, casual observers, panelists, whatever you want to call yourself, because there is something going on.
I do not like what is going on with Jim Nick and how she's being targeted. I am a friend. I am she's said some of the horrible things about about shit.
but it's just, I see what it is. I do not like how a certain person spoke to you today,
Bita, when it came to trying to justify their treatment of Jimnick, considering everything
that Jimnick has disclosed publicly that she's going through. You do not get to monetize stuff
like that or try to make it seem like it's normal or just try to condition people and to be insensitive.
Okay
Yeah, hey everybody. So yeah, so what would that happen like last week? That was I think a week ago
It was maybe a little bit over a week, but uh
Yeah
So but last night I saw he was on with like blackout Andy and I think
Jim Nick and
saw him getting drunk and stuff and then I saw on on a Trishalicious show he was
saying stuff about Trishalicious and and Alex and Tracy like and it was and Alex
knows it was because he has something against me or like people that like me
or something like that so that's what it is
I have no problem with that. I don't have a problem with him. He he like started with me
I was always friendly like in Q2. I got introduced to Q and blogger at the same like the same time
They both like just instantly hated me
But what is squirting or squint at squinting
Who's still who is squinting blogger? Oh, I'm not anymore feeling me
Actually, these glasses aren't my reading glasses, so these are.
Yeah, and like Trisha Licious was noticing too, he was like, he was like on a verge of tears.
Like, he's like, when you talk to people, they brought up Trisha's name, and then he like kicked both of them off the panel.
And he's like, don't talk, and he gets tears in his eyes.
What else?
Oh, and Blackout Andy is in love with Paige.
And he's like, he's looking for Paige.
And yeah, oh my god, he's in love with Paige.
And he's creepy.
I'm in love with Paige.
Oh my god, he talks like Elmer Fudd or something.
I just don't like him because he porn-bought me several times.
So I keep trying to say hi.
It could be nice to him and stuff.
You know I'm friendly.
So yeah, he was like saying stuff about Paige and stuff. I was like, oh my god
Paige I saw Paige the other day she came in here and then she went to be this and then I guess be the told her not to
Come over here. So don't ever have them now. Yeah, she just because she was gonna come here and then she didn't
So she was on beautiful. I haven't seen her since and so I'm thinking
Yeah, a lot of people were told to take a side
And, of course, usually it's not my side, but I would never have people choose though, right?
Let's see.
And he's a little bit of an oddball, right?
Did he date Jim Nick or something?
I can't believe that.
Anyway, anyway, anyway, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what's going on
sometimes. I'm kind of out of the loop a little bit sometimes. I feel like a little
bit. I don't know. You guys, you don't remember, I've been here like for a short
time. Like people say they, people think they know me for years and stuff like
that, but it's like I've only been streaming place since October, September
January
and so
Yeah
So just warm page. It's a warm page. That is nice. Yeah black. I India the cross and things like
If we has play page, let's play page. Oh
Good Lord anyway
So
Yeah, how's everyone in the chat though?
Thought I'd stop by this morning for a while and miss 30 people in chat. Wow. We had a really good day yesterday to over 80 people in chat
Yeah
Like I just like he's a poor he's a I poor and bombed you I poor I'm poor and bombing you and it's like it was like this really
It was like I don't know what it was. It was it's like some kind of like
Animals vagina or something. I don't know. I don't know it was like didn't look like a porn bomb
But I didn't know what I was looking at it was
For a hole, I don't know
It's Samantha Avery Kate, I don't know
Hey, Glokie
Yeah, but it seemed like I don't went to Samans yesterday and like they were playing like you know the clips of me and stuff
And Christina's there and stuff and
No, I want to thank Summers. Summers was really cool about me. She could have just said, you know, she's a really good friend with Christine. She could have said, oh fuck Psyche, you know, and stuff like that.
Yeah, November or December. But yeah, Summers was like, you know what, I like Psyche. That was just nice to hear. Thank you, somebody says that.
So, that was pretty cool. I don't know why Christine's mad, but...
Because I did play that clip of Christine like you or the same person the exact person who was
Crystal saying the same shit she was saying or different kind of similar shit. She was saying like
You know, I don't even want to say say but she was just saying horrible things
But Christina talking to her and the 15 was dealing with her fight. That's why I kept saying Christine
I could come on Christine like come on the panel. I want I want her to really to respond
And yeah, but she's just mad at me and it's like but I think it's about something else
It's about something else or something because she hasn't been here for weeks and then she just shows up
This is Samantha Kate. I don't know. I don't think Samantha's Kate
I did you have a video called it's Samantha a troll or something like that. It's my shorts in my YouTube shorts
Let's see if I can find it
I know, I mean it's kind of like I was kind of like asking if she was, let me see.
Maybe I figured something out, let me see.
Oh yeah, I see Alex right there.
It says, please have already have blogger threats on file.
Shorts, and I'll get the Samantha one.
Shorts, find this one.
Search.
Okay, oh yeah.
Is chatter Samantha a troll?
Here, here we go.
Samantha, I'm going to see you.
No, you couldn't you didn't hear me what my headphones weren't even on you might have it might have heard
I don't know if my tablet can hear very well. I have my headphones were on. Thank you. It's up easy. Hey, what's up easy?
I thought Samantha
bud
You showing bud Guillermo
So it was someone named bud was from okay apparently okay, whatever I don't know
There's some read a slander and trash or instead of shitting her down. Yeah, but I'm not about I'm not about shutting people down
It's like it really was like it was like slander has to be like something believable. It has to be something like oh
You know, it was just like it was just so ridiculous
My mind I was so ridiculous that it was like it was kind of funny just like what she was like
They say you beat fozzy or something like that and it's like it's not funny, but it's like
just so outrageous and Christina was even like saying,
oh my god, like, she is.
If she was reacting like that before,
and the stuff was being said,
like, I don't understand why it's like, now she's.
J-Dog, are you bullying Samantha?
Don't bully Samantha, come on.
Is it Kate?
I don't know.
I don't think it's Kate, I think, because you know what?
J-Dog, Samantha's usually here when I start the show.
And I don't think Kate would be like that much of a fan
Okay, I
Don't think she's I don't think she's a Kate. I know Kate's account
Kate might have somebody named. That's the guy's name or she has like some kind of like
Somebody that she was I forgot the other name there was like some kind of weird name some guy's name
Yeah, well
Thank you. Yeah, yeah
But I yeah, she's always she's here
That's she's modded because she's here like like one of the first people always and every chats like start chatting and she's so you know I
Think it's been during like Kate's show one and she's been there too, so I
Think out I'm pretty good at like fine like susting out energy. I just never thought that I
Can't you never really know who's behind the account?
somebody else, right?
Yeah.
So, I'll vouch for, I'll vouch for Samantha.
They'll be nice, they'll be nice to Mods, right?
Other Mods.
Yeah, there's, we're gonna respect people,
like, I wish I could find that other video I have,
I don't know why I did with it.
Oh, no, okay, let's see.
Okay, I can put it in here.
The back.
Oh, okay, I have it.
I do, I do, I do, okay, I want to export.
Hold on once again.
Watch this guys, you're gonna really enjoy this.
It just has to download, okay.
Yeah, yeah, co-exist guys, co-exist.
I'll play this tonight, I don't know, I don't know what's up today, like um,
what am I gonna do today? It's Wednesday, I think I might need some coffee,
J-Dog, no harassing, female chatters, okay?
Um, oh, okay, save to desktop, oh, okay, show in folder, where is it? Okay, found it, found it, okay.
This is one of the better ones I've done, okay, so I'll just share it.
Okay, yeah.
Yes, here we go.
More than a livestream,
it's a gathering in the shadow and the light. We face chaos,
comedy, and the unknown together.
With open panels that never shy away from the truth, I am Psyche, your guide through
tarot, prophecy, and the unfiltered clash of voices.
Tonight, we're stepping into the panel verse where allies and trolls alike reveal themselves
in every card turn.
Every word spoken is part of the story.
So stay sharp, stay curious, because once the gates open, anything can happen.
The show is about to begin.
Let's go.
That was the closest I could get to the look.
I tried to make my own custom avatar, and I wasn't doing it right or something,
and so I just went for the Jesus.
I kind of look like I'm dumb.
I don't know.
I kind of got to kick out of that, though.
Oh gosh
Guys are we fighting?
What I think about Howard certain things so he said he was trolling Andy Cohen or something like that
He was like he was just kidding. He's not cancelled and he's gonna go back to the show
I don't know. I think that probably something happened. There was like maybe a backlash
I wanted to see how their reaction would be
and then make a decision based on that, like see if you learn to see if anyone cared before, like, oh, it's time, I don't know, I don't know.
You know, I'm sure he doesn't want to be working anymore, I mean, it's like, it does work for like, the long hours and stuff, and...
Yeah.
Yeah, well, yeah, it's crazy, like, you know, it's like, there's a lot of double standards I know of this, like, you know, it's like...
I can't say it's about these people, but it's like, oh, these people, you go ahead and like, no, say anything you want, right?
It's like, so, the J-DOT, come on.
I'm adding the key notes. I think, though it happens, I think that everyone here is pretty nice.
I just want to get along.
Let's, let's, but yeah, it is, there are...
Some double standards. I know it was like, but that's what you know, it was really cool yesterday though
And I really appreciate everybody for an outdoor outing
Yeah, I mean I can go I mean it's like
I'm a little
Little a little a little bit low on funds right now, but Friday maybe
That's like
So many would like to sponsor and I will grow because I do have some I do have data. I just don't have
fish taco and fish taco stuff today
so
Yeah, but yeah, let's I think I think everyone to go. I think everyone should be respected and like, you know, even
people that
I don't go on walks anymore because it's kind of expensive and it's like
9.13. Wow, three days left of this? I only get a week.
So anyway guys, I do have exciting news. Yeah.
Okay, yeah, I might just, I might end this, well I don't know if I'll end this stream right now,
but yeah, stop fighting. Can you guys stop fighting now please? Yeah, there are double standards and
You know, we should like try to be fair for everybody, right?
Hey
Some you know what I put my music on
On this site called mix cloud, okay
mixcloud is like soundcloud but it's like, you know, I want to try it for it, so here we go, mixcloud
and, oh, mixcloud
but actually it's like, so this, somebody kind of like, you know, a big DJ or something like one of my songs
I mean, and it's this one
uh, playlist
I feel like I've been, oh, I feel like I've been locked out
Spam my soul away, I shouldn't have thought out
A part of my brain was fried
I thought that I could win, but the chat just sighed
Won't you banish me?
They said I wasn't reasonable, nothing was to blame
i tried to flood and pour one over all the mods who fed me but what they didn't see is that i am still me me
baby don't i am still
Gonna take a taxi
Yeah, you're starting trouble in the chat, I can't have that.
Okay, I don't know.
It's like, just stop, just leave him alone.
You can actually like, block He-Man, yeah.
Just block, you just have to touch the meme
and just not, hey, what's up?
You just took a taxi?
Yeah, oh, thank you, you gotty.
I know, but J-Dog, I'm just saying,
So they go it's like even fighting about it for like 20 minutes, and it's like not
Things resolved, and it's just causing problems in the chat
Hey, you gotty
You took a cab to the that's actually based on all these at least a drug on a time
Yeah, and it's called dark side of the city
I'm gonna take a taxi. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah, that's all I saw. Yeah, so it's because
don't want everybody everybody upset you can't come up but have a one-car
renew for the day okay well I'm gonna do it this new this new deck God I know
you don't like these sometimes it's horrible this is the cool one Felix
knocked pull up one car renew for Gotti
a run in Stimpy, you know, yeah, okay.
Yeah, it's a very cool deck, I don't know,
it's very, it's a good deck, really cool too.
So, I'll revise the Picasso a little bit.
Yeah, these are new cards, these are called
the Felix Knocked Gallery of Hallucinations Oracle.
Okay, I did some reading yesterday.
Oh, I want to thank Kel, Kelly,
and I want to thank J-Dog and
I want to thank also Alex, everybody's, all of them have really supported with
readings and stuff like that. Okay, so Gotti, enticement? Okay, so maybe if there's
gonna be some kind of like offer, but it's like you just have to be, you know,
just watch the offer because I might be trying to...
Distract or entice you about something. No, maybe are you trying to entice somebody?
I don't know that you've got it that you like you at all you like it okay, but it says enticement, so maybe
some kind of like you know
Offer what is this going on here? Looks like there's a looks like the there's a serpent in the tree, too
The tree right there. I'm gonna be like an early Adam and Eve kind of thing. This will really happen in the garden
I'm not sure but
You entice the world. I'm going to pull a couple more cards for God, because this is like one card's not enough. I need three.
Okay, well that's the, that's the, uh, okay. What does this say?
This one says, let's say secrets, hold up.
Yeah, this one says secrets. There's some secrets. Someone has a secret, someone knows a secret.
There's whispering going on. They're talking about somebody in a house or something.
Uses there.
I don't know if that makes sense to you. I'll pull one more.
Snow Blossom. Snow Blossom is a flower, magical flower, it's fire.
Maybe like it's kind of herb or like it's kind of
But if you're feeling left out in the cold or something like that there's gonna be something to warm you up
I thought that right something to warm you up. I don't think you'd be left out for that long, okay
so
Well, so anybody would like reading you love you hate snow. It's the flower be cool. Yeah a little fire flower
Yeah, that that's secrets kind of scary. Oh the ketchup on the stick. I like a one sauce ketchup on the stick
I kind of like like hamburger steak. I like I like ketchup on that. It tastes like hamburgers, but you're welcome
I hope you like that
Anybody else would like a card out of the deck he man or Nancy or anybody in the chat
Well, I got him out. I'm gonna show up with him right now. I
Love anyone. I like a one. I like I like Lee and parents. I'm more sure
Some good shit. I love it. You know, steak is just delicious. I haven't had a good steak in a while.
Yeah. Okay. Nancy.
Nancy, you got the Awake card, okay?
So I don't know if you've had insomnia or something, or if there's something keeping you awake, or there's some kind of something.
But...
Look, there's a little, like, little devil peeking through the window and stuff like that.
You're awake.
And, uh...
It's an interesting card, though.
It's like, but I would take this to mean, like, you're very aware of something,
or you become aware, or you are awake about something, you know?
Kind of like the woke thing.
You're, like, you're just aware, you're, like, aware, and it kind of...
Shook you out of sleep or something like that. I'll pull a couple more for you, too
This is nice this one says ephemera ephemera is like something that's like it's like a short but that's a short time, right I
Would say this is kind of like enjoy like the scenic route route enjoy the little things like you know
Little drives little
Little experiences, you know, life is short and
You gotta enjoy the ride, right? Finally for Nancy
This one says departure are you leaving somewhere or somebody like there's that you're leaving something
Okay, and then someone's gonna miss you. I don't think it looks like kind of like
That you got you
She said the bus stop. I think this might be her ex-boyfriend. I
Don't know if that makes sense to you Nancy, but
Leaving something behind that's what I got for you
Hey, Schrodinger's cat
Panel I don't know if I have a panel of oh
You like God you'd like to visit cemeteries
Link you the panel okay, I got you you want to come up Schrodinger's cat, okay?
Who are you?
Have you been on here before?
Here's the link.
Um, I do like cemeteries. I mean, it's like, you know,
and in Hinduism, they have these burial grounds and they have a lot of people in India, right?
Which oh that guy okay. How well shorting area
So in India they have something called like Kali tantra and it has Empress Chinchilla
Well Empress Chinchilla you're a porn bomber. That's why you're blocked. I mean that's why I had to block you of course
And are you in your man too aren't you a man named Empress Chinchilla
I'll have you on with the being up, yeah.
But I don't block people on Streamlabs
unless they form up, that's the only reason I would.
The only reason I'd block anybody on Streamy
or if they form up, if you promise not to,
I suppose I can give you a try, I mean,
it's like, are you, see the air of your ways?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I think it's like, um, you know, there's like Gaga and there's
Satan there's somebody named Satan Gaga. There's one named John Woo
There's someone named. I just know I know all the names now. I've been poor mom over a hundred times and a lot of them have the same name
Okay, I'm pretty sure it's blocked. Okay, so I'm gonna unblock but
You porn bomb
Empress Chinchilla will be banned, permanent banned.
I'm gonna give you one more chance.
Let me have a look.
Empress Chinchilla, there you are. 2.0.
Gotcha. Okay, you're off.
And I will read some of these names.
Okay, so we have Daniel Larson, John Woo.
Nugget service, Mr. Crubble, Mondo, Garmento,
Mursal, Rudolph Haas, Roger Claude, Empress Chinchilla,
there you are again.
Amanda Hugginkiss, Larry Nash, that's Sieg,
a Royal, Artie Flanders, Petty Wab,
Bala Ben, Bala Ben, Mojojo Juniper,
but I don't think it's the real one,
I think it's somebody just using that name.
Ben Rahman, that's a form bomber.
James Monzo, Tamille Tame,
Change Schrodinger is that you again? Okay, you're ban on three accounts. I'm Schrodinger. It's not looking good for you
And then Schrodinger's cat. Why are you ban on four accounts? You bet you perform them five times
What are you thinking you can't come up?
There's four of your alts on this here. No wonder you can't get up
Well, unfortunately, I've just unbanned all the Schrodinger's, you know, alts, but we'll see, you're not, I will recognize it.
Anyway, you know, you know who is mean? Yesterday was like, I used to like this guy, the loser, and he, not the loser, no, the loser is cool.
It's the guy named, oh my God, I can't remember his name now, it's like, you know, it's, oh, nobody, N-O-B-O-D-Y, it's a zero for the O.
He's like okay, so Christine brought up like she's like oh and you see there's this guy Mason
And he has like the brain of like a twelve-year-old boy or something
And then he's like oh my god sake. He's sick. Hey guys, Mason is 35 years old
Okay, and also he doesn't live in a group home
He lived in a group home for a period of time because his mom was he said his mom was
Like you know on the street or something so he was in a group home
And he's on SSI right, but it's like he's perfectly intelligent, and he's
I don't know. It's like it just made it sound like I was doing something wrong
I was just I'm just joking around first of all. I'm not really attracted to him, you know at all
But I think it's kind of funny like his reaction. I don't know maybe some people go against but
I'm just playing around. Hey, Jamie. How are you?
Yeah, you know who you but you Jamie, you know who was on Sandman's and and beat is yesterday. I mean or all the time, you know
All of a sudden it's come out of their shell
All right
Yeah, I can't believe I had just unbanned and Christian chill out on four accounts
Herbal
Yeah
So, yeah, Jamie's Cowboys. There is a video with Jamie's Cowboys. I think Jamie's Cowboys tried to quit and they kicked my wrench, they kicked my wrench, and I was like, nope.
So that's one of the videos. If Psyche refuses to un-mod Jamie's Cowboys, they'll be expelled.
So...
Well, I know that Jamie like does see some stuff like you know
She's you guys go to some chats and like watch them and she doesn't like and she sees some people that are mods like
Not even like not defending me, but like maybe like
Piling on I don't know. I'm not sure I don't know
I don't know it's like I'm very very very willing to be okay, so
Okay, so we have rain coming up I told I told rain I would let her on it might be for a very short time because I
Don't know if I trust this now why I trust rain, but I don't trust hello
Okay fail they failed that was a fail that was called I they failed
Hold on, hold on.
Hello?
Rain.
It's just, I think it's somebody porn bombing.
I didn't see backstage.
There's some kind of weird picture.
Can't really tell what it is, though.
Oh, hold on, hold on.
Hello?
You're muted, hello?
You meet yourself. What's going on?
I'm not gonna let you on stage
That you rain no, okay
I'm kicking you out of the studio
The person just sitting backstage like switching their photo around and stuff. I
Don't I sassy I wouldn't say that that our word I wouldn't say that
Dad, I think when I think of the R word, I think of like, you know, like a Mormon Down syndrome kind of
Thing, right? Yeah, I know
Yeah, no, he's perfectly intelligent, I
Can tell he's intelligent because he gets inside jokes like he even makes fun of me like a little bit so it's like
obviously got some kind of
intelligence
He also plays the drums too, and he's also, I like his, I like his lap, but yeah, he's a little bit like, you know
also, he's been kind of like going after like the ladies, like, you know,
Spunky and
Somebody else was like, oh my god, he was saying some stuff to me or something. I don't remember exactly who else it was
But so I'm just kind of like, you know, give him a little taste of his own medicine. Let him know it's like, you know
I'm bad.
Guys, that's why I didn't hang up on Crystal too, it's like because I like to have people
reveal themselves and I'm not saying Crystal or Christine was real, I'm saying Crystal
was real but I'm saying that.
And Amason's funny, he's a really good person, he's a sweetheart of a person, he's not, and
it's like not like, I remember we're gonna meet him right, it's like it's just a joke,
I mean, he, I think hopefully, you know, it's just a joke.
I don't I don't know that that's what that's what it was he mad. I think I don't know Jamie. Are you cool?
if they he man, but I just know like, you know
She's other feelings are okay, so this is that a is that a real Arthur. I think that might be a real Arthur hole
No
Mr. Psyche, long time, bro. This is the new Arthur. How you doing there? This is actually RG. How you doing there, Psyche? Long time.
Hey, what's up, RG? How are you doing?
Hey.
I'm doing good, man. I'm feeding my puppy here scribbles. How you doing?
Hey, I'm doing great. I'm doing great.
Well, okay, so the racer reign is back, but I don't believe it's a real racer.
So if it's a real racer reign, go into the chat and say...
Hi, it's it's rain. I want to come say hi or something like that. Don't just sit back stage
So why would you have an S as for your name first of all?
Schrodinger's cat
Why are you going under rain's name just go under I was gonna let you on a Schrodinger. Why are you doing?
What's going on psych? How you doing there, brother? I'm doing okay. I'm just trying to dodge these porn bomb
same
psych um I
Have a couple questions, but before anything I would love to give a shout out to the one and only trip kick
He's out there being
As unbiased as possible. He's providing the clips of you and be the
And as much as Vita wants to say, well, show me the clip, show me the clip, I never said that before. Thank you for calling 1495 for shipping and handling, you know, as much as she wants to talk all this shit.
Guess what? There's somebody out there who's unbiased, who's not picking the side, and who's simply providing the content straight down the middle.
And anybody with a brain can see how Vita talks a lot of ish about you.
And, you know what I find disgusting when people blame the alcohol, blame it on the a, a, a, a, a, a, a, alcohol, you know, it's like, come on, I'm gonna say this and I'm gonna say this always, a sober man's thoughts is a drunk man's words.
Yeah, well, you know what, it's like, I do feel like she's been kind of harsh on me, like especially...
Like some of the name calling because she's like, oh, well, I get upset. She's like, well, why is he getting so upset and like his feelings?
It's like
It's not when the trolls do it. It's when she would do it and stuff like that
She has I'll say she's defending me and stuff
She defended me with with my cast and she and she knows and but she's also said some
Not nice words about me. Like, you know, maybe an anger. Maybe I've said I've done the same thing me with her
You know and so but
Too wrongs will make it right. You know, the most I've ever heard you say anything about her is you called there a bitch
Yeah, I did I did once
Yeah, she's coming
And not for nothing, but I think gay words have a bitch pass like you guys could see that and there should be no issue
Like you guys can call another woman that like hey bitch
Yeah, I know but it's like yeah
I'm not allowed to do anything
I'm always like singled out for everything. I mean it's like really like I never see other people could single out as much as I
Like oh look what he's doing and it's like, but you know what yesterday in Sandman's chat
Like people got it people were like saying
It was a double standard people were saying well like what it's like there was like what did he do?
He's like he like he like docks you or like, you know send like a you know
Horses head to your house or something like that. All I did was he made an AI song that wasn't even like offensive
I mean it was like I thought it was the attention was it was gonna be a cute a cute song
We risk going back and forth. She was doing the same kind of joke about
stupid biscuit thing. But she can joke all about that all she wants and it's like I do
one little song about it. I'm not talented because AI is just easy, she can make better
AI songs than me. And then she's insulted my tarot reading report, but she has been
like pretty supportive lately of saying, oh well Psyche, he wants to be doing tarot,
or he should be doing tarot. I do tarot, and I do tarot on TikTok, and I do tarot here.
But it's like not everybody is like that
Into it. I can't I can't run the whole show doing it. I can I can interweave it more into the show
but
It is a lot of energy
You know
There's that and then I also have another question if you mind yeah, but
Of course
You're muted.
Arthur? Arthur?
Well, he's muted. Well, you guys see like there's like some kind of like movie about the crack epidemic in like the 70s
and I think it was in Detroit or somewhere in Michigan, and it's like in good times, but like he was like
put his face on the guy's body and he was like dancing, like he was like flip-walk and stuff like that.
Anybody see that I did like salmon show though. It's just because it's like, you know, I
Think his audience gets it like like they
There was like a little bit of hypocrisy going on where it's like wow
It's like people really have been going after me and it's like I really I'm respond to some stuff. That's white boy Rick. Okay. Oh
Yeah, white boy Rick. Yeah, that's what his name was there was white boy Rick and he was like this white guy
that was like a police informant when he was like 14 years old and then he ended up like
being one of like the biggest like crack dealers I guess not as big as like the big dogs like he's
like he said he sold like you know ten kilos that's like a hundred kilos or something like that
but yeah he ended up getting arrested he's been in prison for a long people longer than
had a murder and things like that it's still in prison because they have such strict crack cocaine laws.
Because of racism and then he
ironically
He got swept up in that part of it. I'm really I'm really for uh, I
Think most of the crime comes from
The criminalization of it that's what causes the crime to decriminalize and all of a sudden
Like this is it during prohibition the same thing happened with alcohol all of a sudden they had a black market for it
demand, because for men, the men didn't go away. It's just like, then all of a sudden the black market, then like,
you know, the MAFIA could take over for it. Hey, what's up random index? Thank you for
visiting my
Twitch stream, and
yeah, please comment in the Twitch stream, and
thank you.
What, cheap followers on stream, boo? Okay, I'll check it out.
stream boo. Well, I don't really want to buy followers for it. I'm going to try to do like some more like
networking. I've been doing a lot of really good networking on Snapchat and Facebook and
Instagram. You go to PsycheAwakens.com. There should be links to all my social
things. I'm on X, I'm on Instagram, I'm on Facebook.
I got a lot, I'm on a lot of stuff, but you can see all the links on PsycheWeekings.com
How are we doing guys? So what else do we have?
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know what's going on today.
She's live, but you've tried, she's nice.
But she's tired or yeah, I mean poor Jim Nick is like, you know really going through some medical issues right now
And then it's like she's being really picked on it. I've seen I've seen it happen like for a while like the big certain
Panel guests and stuff just being really disrespectful to her and oh
There he goes so but I like to make a lot
Yo
You're muted, but you said you had a question for me, so go ahead sir
So, anything else going on today, guys? Let me know about the news. I don't know if anyone has anything interesting to bring up.
I don't know if I'll be here too long.
So, give me a while you can.
okay
i'm filling out some things
hello
i cannot tell you
hey tree frog how are you
you see it
I don't have that Spotify artist.
I need to get one.
Instagram, I do have an Instagram username,
at
Psyche.
Awakens.
Okay.
A musical style.
How would I describe it?
I would say,
electronic
what do i like? what my kind of music do i like? i like country music
i like secondary pop
reality nancy is that you?
no, it's shorting your cat again
shorting your cat, you're not fooling me, i can see your name
okay? stop it
She's welcome to, of course, but I just never seen her, so I'll, already, I was suspicious of the user.
Okay, electronic, I'll do acid house, side trance, that's the name for me.
Is there a witch house? I like witch house too. Okay, country music, okay.
I like hip-hop and rap.
not christian rap though
it's crying on the trip
um...
not really into it, i like melodic metal okay
pop by like commercial mainstream, electric pop and uh...
funk, rhythm, sound, soul, okay so...
moods, okay, so that's my moods
okay, i would say
i'm catchy, i think i'm catchy
Sometimes dreamy, I think eccentric a little bit. I think some of this dark, experimental,
good vibes, energetic, meaningful lyrics, offbeat, underground, unique, and backwards.
Okay, I'm going through some steps with some website right now.
Post my picture
Where is a known man
Oh
This is if this is a Schrodinger again, I want to begin
Hello, yeah, my bad. Yeah, I think he's going off real quick. I do have a question real quick
You and Dottie always go at it and then you guys are good and then you're bad and you're good. I hate you your block
No wrench, your wrench, your mod. No wrench, no mod. Now I see that he's a mod. What is
going on with that? Knowing that he has clearly form bombed you, him and his friend, but
yeah, you decide to give him a wrench. What are the standards to being a mod here? What
are the guidelines when you are a mod? And what is it that it takes to become a mod?
Wrench, but yet this individual who has porn bomb you in the past
It's clearly a mod here and I guess
It's just very confusing. That's all as a viewer. I'd love to know
What's the question again, sorry
What are the guidelines? What does it take in order to become a mod? Once you are a mod, what are the rules?
Keep wanting to like remod you and stuff, but then I remember like I keep remodding you and then you immediately like usually like start misbehaving, right?
OK, I mean, not for me, not for me, brother, but for Gotti.
Gotti doesn't do anything.
I mean, all I'm saying is Gotti's is a buying mod.
Like, he knows some people that are, I think everybody's mod,
but yeah, I think I have probably the most trolls
with wrenches and any cat on YouTube, by the way.
No, I know another channel.
I know another channel, trust me.
I mean, it's fine.
I mean, it's like, as long as the trolls are, like, working for me, like, and, you know,
and they're using their trolls against, like, you know, bad people, but it seems like that
they always go after me and stuff, so, or, like, you know, I don't know, and I, I just,
uh, like, yesterday, I'm honest, Sebastian, within five minutes, he was hiding people.
Like that we're saying stuff about him, like personally, like, you know, oh, and so I was like, well, I'm modern, but like, I was like, yeah, I can't have mods through a person.
If you beg me, like, help me have it back, and he's like, I won't do it again, and like, he's gonna, he knows what to do right away.
I give it back to him, two minutes later, he's hiding people again, so I just can't.
And then he asks, then he keeps asking again for it back, you know.
I know, I know.
I think you should definitely consider having Dixon as a mod.
I think you could trust him.
He's very trustworthy
Dixon, I don't know. Where have I heard that name before? Mason, though, Mason Dixon line. That's it, right?
That's all I know.
Okay, well, I'm gonna mod, uh, Dixon. I need to
I need to get a little trust in him. Dixon, congratulations.
There you go. Hey, Spunky.
Smash, what about you as a mod?
Smash, so who are, are you Hebrew Hammer, Smash?
I do have another question.
What are your thoughts on Howard Stern,
his contract getting terminated?
I heard that was a joke.
I heard that he's going to be back too.
He was trolling Andy Cohen or something like that about being fired, hating someone funky.
I think, but yeah, I think it just came out that he is going to go back to his show, so.
El Dorado, El Doe wants some, is that the real El Doe?
What are you talking about? Where's your wrench?
El Doe?
Are you done with your crusade against me?
But why do you hate me so much, El Doe?
I think, uh, you need to apologize to me, though.
Who is Dixon? I don't know who Dixon is.
Yeah, XOA!
I don't know who Dixon is.
So, that's not Eldo, okay. Eldorado kid, you are not.
It's not a very good person to come up as if you're going to get back at me
If it was a real elder and then he apologized I might consider it
You'll suck me off. Well, let me look at the face. Oh, this is me. I want
Listen to picture guys
What is that? Is there nudity? Oh, no, I'll suck you off. Wow. And who's in that picture though?
You're looking at you
So, okay
Any other questions Arthur any other
interrogations like what do you think about all this beta stuff or the how about the you mentioned the blogger stuff or what do you think
Do your blogger is fun that stuff I think I think beta
Constantly makes up with people then goes at them constantly goes that and then the tags, you know, she's you got to be careful with a parent Alex honestly
You know they they they're friends with you one minute and then the next they're against you you have to be careful
You know if if you've seen it happen to other people what makes it any different that they won't do it to you
I'm a different person than other people and it's like also like I
Will treat them well on my show too
Like maybe something they do get overwhelmed and I may or not on the panel when I should be sometimes, but I'm basically
Oh, you're 15 or 15 out the panels. Oh my gosh
Well, I'm gonna say is just whatever secrets you have man keep it to yourself
Don't bother telling anyone man. They're just gonna use it against you. You know, I don't have any secrets. That's the thing
I think I
Yeah, can't even have a secret
Everybody is always trying to
To I guess all the secrets of everybody so I'm I really don't have any I'm pretty much open book, but
Welcome to the madness
Buckle in time. Can you send me a deck?
More more music
Playlist next
I'm gonna do it until 10 a.m. And I think it's just turn 10
Records for the chat.
So a duck and a frog walk into a bar and then the bartender goes, hey, it's a really cute
duck you got there.
Okay, oh, hold on.
There's another one.
And then what happens, everybody started to laugh hysterically.
It is not a good, oh, thank you El Dorado.
I mean, I just saw, she said maybe, she said things that I wouldn't say to my enemies.
I got over, like, you know, I just, you know, I'm trying to get a story from money or like,
you know, where you can get like, congrats? No, I'm not gonna, you give me a hit to that.
Plus.
I had the reputation that I didn't do the polls.
Well, she does look a little bit nuts, but she also seems logical too.
I had a bad mood because of her.
Okay.
Sorry, I
Thought I was like talking for like five minutes. I was like, oh my god
Ari
Jamie's cowboys was calling. Thank you for calling it trying to call Jamie. Oh, I did fall asleep
I'm fine. I didn't have my coffee yet. So thank you, Jamie
I need to go get some coffee a little bit. Do you have it? I send bagels
charisma is a great odd she's always nice to me I think she I think charisma
gets it like and she might have come here to like maybe initially to troll or
something like that but she's never given me a problem at all but I understand
like maybe there's another chat but she is a different aim but you know I'm
Super is my pictures.
Well, I guess I'll just use my...
jesus
yeah so i do have some exciting stuff going on
smaller
I'm releasing a song today. Today I'm going to go release Dark Side of the Lifestream or the Troll Side of the Lifestream.
I just search the web, Google, Google search, add my track, I get one track, not very many.
Can you release it today? What is today 9? Is it 9-11?
I don't know. Is it?
What's today? Oh, shit.
It was really weird. I was looking last night under the name...
There were channels named Psyche Awakens Channel, and I was like, oh my god, and it's like they're new.
It's like I'm not like troll channels or just like other people that were actually what I mean. It's like you waitin
But then there's like I found a picture and it looks just like me and I said psyche on I was like what the hell it was just so weird
It wasn't me. I don't think so at least
At least they today is the 10th. Okay tomorrow's the 11th
Is it an unfinished song? No. Does its track have lyrics? Yes, my track has lyrics. They're in English, okay?
Okay, what kind of links can you use? Okay, so now I can
Put the sound that hopefully the mixed plug link on
invalid link okay see it shit is it okay spotify okay that worked
sorry guys
I guess I can choose a company or something
oh I can put it on a playlist
Okay, one Pro Selected, two.
Cool, I'm sorry guys.
Pop, before, yeah, I didn't think that,
I tried that one.
Oh, it did, it worked, okay.
Here we go. Hello. Hey, how are you? Good, how are you? Do you know about what happened last night?
I saw some of it, yeah, with Vlogger, right? I didn't see it live. I got clips this morning
and people had already called in where I am, what he said.
That's some pretty horrible things and
What do you think his issue is do you think that it's only drinking or do you think it's something else?
well, he was
Acting very kind of strange because I think he had a blackout Andy and then like Jim Nick on and then like
They brought up I think about Patricia's name and then he got like very upset like you see his eyes start to water a little bit like almost like
Trisha knows she's like, he's almost like he's crying and he was like half naked some of the time and
You know, it's an underwear walking around and I don't know. He was definitely drunk
Yeah
Do you think that it's possible that he was told to say some of those things
Rather than it just be like
From his core
I don't know, like, I don't know who would, like,
unless, like, that'd be kind of, like, very...
I know. It's far out, yeah.
It's, like, out of the realm of normal possibilities.
You know, Tracy, like, Tracy, I think Tracy more right now.
He was saying... Well, he threatened her, too.
Somebody was watching the whole thing,
and they sent me, like, a synopsis, okay?
Like, he threatened Trisha, me...
And Tracy, and I hadn't even thought about Tracy in a very, very, very long time.
I know she takes issue with me, but she has been so kind to blogger, but you know what
all three of us women have in common?
We all like you.
I don't know if that's a factor.
Yeah, you guys, we need to bring it up.
Like he, like I, I, yeah.
I think I got brought I think he brought my name last night. Maybe like I think he was like
multiple times multiple times
I have about 10 clips. I don't have the full streams. I have about 10 clips
And he brought you up a bunch
I think that there's a lot of things that play like I had to do what you know
I have to you know, say what I need to
Stay and sign what I need to sign when it comes to protecting myself law enforcement wise
but do you think that
Part of the reason maybe he's jealous of you is because he wishes he could be as open and free as you are I
Mean well like I would I'd like to think that like
But it's like it seems like he was like he was saying like the
N-word a lot last night like everything that it back in I did a stream a few moments ago about this
In February of 2024, he was trying to get me to strike Trisha's channel, which I didn't do and everything that he said that she did back in February of last year is what he did literally beyond that even last night.
Yeah, she was like she was like, oh, she's I think she kept trying to start she was saying Alex like if you want to
Or I think she's saying Alex. He's like if you want to strike him like you know, he's saying this like right you can strike him and stuff
or something
I don't know okay when I met him and everything like I don't think we ever got along like that well
But I really don't I thought it was I was down like he wasn't like this before he was not
I've known of him since he first appeared in these communities
I'm not sure if he's been honest or not about having a woman through the car diverse truthfully
He claims that but nobody remembers him. I think that he was fixated. I think he's in love with Trisha. I really do
But he doesn't know how to deal with it and I think that he observed her for many, probably at least two years before actually talking to her and I was kind of, you know, the facilitator to get them to talk, but he sabotaged that.
And I was sad when that happened because, but I'm not sad now because I don't want to show around him. Honestly, no, no, no. But they would have been a cute couple truthfully that they really because they're both very petite little, you know, people, they're little.
But not the way he is now. I mean, she could never have somebody like that around her child. Absolutely not.
That's why I have a hard time even looking at that for what it is because he did not used to be that way
You can tell like when I'm like, I guess they give Nick and
Andy like
teasingly brought up Trisha's name like Tim and then he like kicked them off the panel
Like and then he was like getting his eyes started to water and stuff like that and he started it was like
It's weird. It's like yeah, he has some kind of like emotions people are trying to turn him against
Black now blackout Andy really wants that leads to be a solid friend
I don't think that blogger has been a good friend of blackout, but I think blackout has been a good friend of blogger
And I don't like the way that that other woman was talking to blackout at all.
And there's things about blackout and I told you that I do understand him to an extent because of certain things.
I just have an issue with him because he pornbombed me several times including the other night. I don't agree with him pornbombing
I don't agree with him stalking. I you know, I don't agree
But I do understand a certain reason as to why he's angry and it did come out last night
People are very unjustly mean to him
who have no reason to be mean to him.
And they say some things to him that I know
are very hurtful to him, but he doesn't stay it,
but I know that they are.
So I don't know.
This is like blogger, but it's like kind of teasing
his speech impediment a little bit.
And then it's like, he kind of laughed,
but it's like, I was wondering if it bothered him.
Blogger himself has a slight speech impediment.
I mean, he does, he has a list, very slight, but it's there.
He he needs to get his bicuspids taken out and his front teeth pulled back with braces that would remedy that
He was he's a little guy though. I was surprised what he was like. Yes
He's very petite very petite. He's
only about
Maybe
Maybe five three
He's very small
Yeah
Yeah, and I think you know maybe
Maybe it's because I'm tall or something. I don't know but also I did a stream about it
I was like because you two facially do
Not exactly alike. I think that you actually have a nicer face than he does but
He wouldn't look at you, you know, just like how you're sitting right now. He would look it would be it would it would probably
it would irritate him to an extent.
And then your popularity is rising right now.
But then on top of that,
just as he's on the shorter end,
you're on the taller end.
So imagine if you're a short person,
but I guess your saving grace would always be your face,
but then you come across somebody with a similar face,
but they're tall, like you wanna be
Oh my gosh
That that would be a little bit of a mind fuck. It just would
Yeah, and he um, I remember like
Probably a couple months after I met it was of yeah a couple months
And he started the calling himself blogger awakens tarot like it holds the mouse's name and he's like I'm gonna be a hero reader
I'm gonna I'm gonna read like methadone leaves or something like that
I say I'm gonna go to the methadone clinic and read the I don't know. He was like it was like a brilliant
Yeah, I saw it. I saw it. I thought that was
So he's watched you for a while.
He's probably, he's threatened.
He's a little threatened by you, that's interesting.
Well, you know, there's people that,
cause I've been on for a short time,
like I think there's people that have been around
for like a while, like not only in this,
like in this genre, but like on YouTube,
it's like there's a lot of people
that have been around for like a long time.
And it's like and and they I don't know. I don't know how big is how big was Bogger's chat?
I wasn't really in his chat. I just saw some clips like from the screenshots that I saw no more than 50
Well, 15 is not I mean, that's not bad. Like I like yesterday. I actually got over 80 viewers at one point
It was like it was and I was on for like six hours. There's one of my most successful videos and everything
Awesome. Yeah, it's really good and it's like
It was also, like a lot of, it wasn't like too much hate at all, it was interesting.
Plus, when I went to Sam Man's to like, just watch what they were playing, except me and
like the Christine stuff and all that, and in Sam Man's audience, like a lot of people
in that room, it's like more than I've ever seen in other rooms, there were like, like
a lot of them were on my side, like in kind of saying it.
People like it's like you do they're like it was harpy on psyche. Like he didn't really do anything like people like you people like you
Reflectors like it's like a nice to have
Chats on chats kind of on my side about some stuff because I was people see it
It's an interesting. It's an interesting thing. That's kind of balancing out when you think about it. You're growing
People are seeing the real you
It's positive
Other people people are seeing the real them and they're shrinking or diminishing because
It's negative. Yeah, but there was yeah, there's a lot of people are just like lashing out kind of like and just
Acting up and like look all these death threats. I'm getting they're everywhere everywhere everyone wants to get me
I mean, I hope you have like, you know, you can't have mace and stuff like that, you know what I mean?
Look, I have, you know what I have? I have my faith, you know, how I feel about that.
I also have almost an endless supply of sativa and indica.
That's what I'm doing. You know, I'm going to go hiking later today. That's going to be cool.
Yeah, yeah, you know
You don't know much about you know when I was active in the adult industry, but I was getting
Worse than this. It was actually similar
So I've dealt with it before but if I was a different person, I would probably feel differently
But it's to the point to where it's been to such an extent that any time I visit family and their cities or whatnot, I do immediately let law enforcement know, hey, you might get some calls if you do, it's because it's me and they know.
And where I am right now, it's a lot of people who deal with this kind of a thing. They're used to it. And I didn't even know that people have already called in last night. So I feel safe.
You know, I
Only feel like God can take me out, you know, whenever God's ready for me to hang out in heaven. I'll be there
And then I'll become a ghost and when I'm a ghost, I'm gonna haunt people
But I think that'll be, you know, at least half a century from now. So hopefully but
You know, I thought that was weird because
I didn't expect to hear certain things from him that I heard, but I do think it sounded a little forced
Yeah, maybe somebody
I don't know if he's that good of an actor, right?
like but
I was looking at his face
I was I was looking at his face and there I've never I've only spoken to him privately a couple times
and
I have a hard time hating him. I don't hate him. I feel bad for him, like really bad for him, but he has so much potential.
He really does.
Yeah, yeah
Still, I mean, it's like, you know people people can certainly turn things around
I believe but oh, yeah, Tracy did like Tracy has been on my show a few times recently
And then like yeah, that's why he ripped into her like the last night and that's neat list
I mean, I've caught her on your show before you two have a wonderful rapport
Yeah, you can't own
panel guests, you know, I mean, you can have your standards, I guess, as to, you know, what you want to associate with versus what you don't. I feel that same way.
But, you know, Tracy's a little older and she really cares about what she considers her boys, you know, her guys.
For the most part, what all he said to me, I haven't listened to all of it, but I did hear what he had to say when it comes to her. And if you ever see this, Tracy, I'm going to apologize on his behalf when it comes to you. And I know you don't like me, but I am going to apologize on his behalf to you because he's out of his mind.
And he didn't mean what he said to you.
And I don't want her to feel a certain way about that because I know that she legitimately cares I
Think that last time I talked to him
He came in my chat and he was he was in my chat once in a while and like usually he's just kind of trolling in the chat
but
Last time he was in the chat. I was like, oh, do you want a reading and he was like sure then I gave him a reading and he was like
Actually, like he is like he was gracious and he said he liked it and stuff and
so
So that was like I was like, oh good. Like I was like, maybe there's like a glimmer of hope
But I think he even said that he said maybe there's a glimmer of hope for us to be friends or something like that
I don't think he said something like that. I was like, oh, that's what he wants. Yeah, he's he is naturally very
Empathic he's very he feels very deeply and I think that's why you know, he does what he does as far as you know overindulging
whatever it is that he's indulging in. The little that I do know about him he
got picked on a lot not only you know socially in the world but I think you
know in the personal front as well and not you know
I think that the way he naturally is, actually is more along the lines of being, you know,
pseudo-blogger, awakens tarot, if he was braver, if he was braver, he would be able to be that
guy.
But, you know, I told him a long time ago, you know, his actual skill is...
Finding vintage items or items that people think aren't worth a lot and flipping them and turning over his profit. He's, I always said to him, he should do like a online road show, like antique road show or 80s road show, you know, that kind of era retro road show.
And he never did, but that's his skill. That's his actual talent.
We have an auto and I don't know if you've ever met auto auto. How are you doing today?
Yo
I've seen auto before. Yeah, you see
Good are you gonna are you behaving today or no?
Yeah, man. I'm okay, bro. I'm okay. I'm okay. I mean that's normal as I can gear
Okay
Yeah, it's able to alex and uh, welcome to the show. I
know
How are you doing auto?
Hola, I'm okay
Let me take a break I use the restrooms okay
Okay, how about a break at the restroom there?
Alexandra, okay
So auto where it was where we've been auto. I know last time you were on
Yeah, I didn't I think I was talking to somebody else or I was having some other people on or something and then I don't
I got to you. So I'm sorry about that
but uh, yeah
Are you mad at me about that?
No, bro. No, bro. I'm out at you bro. Fuck. No. Hell. No, bro. I got no reason to be mad at you for what?
Okay, well, I introduce you to 40 diamonds. I don't know if you
Well, I don't think hey a man a bro
Yeah, let me tell you something about myself, man. I really don't
Don't really think about stuff. I don't really think you know what I mean? I just go with the flow
Take it as calm. I don't fucking
I'm not gonna sit there after the fat and then think about things. I have no time for but thank you
Okay, so so no I have no problem with any any diamond or any any blue and white. I got no problem
Okay, I don't know
No one was teasing you or something like that. So but so what's up?
What brings you here today? What do you have to give a message for the chat or
Brings me. I mean, it's just how it is. I just go with the flow whatever
Well, you know, I
Overthink you under
Because you know why you shouldn't overthink because you're exhausting your energy
That's why you shouldn't exhaust your energy by overthinking. You know what I mean?
You shouldn't do that
Yeah
I only try not to trip on stuff, but it's like I do like to like have some introspection and like, you know kind of like
Examining my behavior and stuff like no behavior
I'm sorry go ahead Alexander. Oh, no, no go ahead Otto because I'll I'm very long-winded. I'll talk forever, but you go ahead
Go ahead go ahead. I'm around these streets
But uh, well, I think it was I think it was last night. That's like he had a guest. I don't know what his name is, but he's
He has a beard he has a very deep
Dialect
But he actually gave some really good advice along the lines of auto last night when it came to
Getting in shape. He was saying, you know, if you want to get in shape you got to actually live
the lifestyle of somebody who's in shape.
And he was right, he was totally right.
And I was listening to it, I'm like,
man, he sounds like a fitness instructor.
And it's interesting, because there's he's,
you have-
What's up, Markers?
Hey, Summer.
Hey, Summer, how are you doing?
Wonderful. How's everybody doing? It seems like there's a lot going on these days. Yeah, I just wanted to thank you because I saw
I did see last night on Samman's channel like
Love you to death, but I got some questions for you and Alex actually
Because I'm I don't know what's going on and I mean I'm hearing like happy a hits and all this other crazy shit
So I'm just like what in the hell is going on because
Psyche you have a lot of people and this is no disrespect to you Alex because you're new to me
So no disrespect, but you got a lot of people that have supported you for a very very long time
Very long time and love you to death dude make it frustrating with you from time to time
With rightfully so because you play your part in things as well
But I just think things are a little weird, like, I don't know, what's going on, man?
I know, Bita, well, Bita had, Bita...
I'm not talking about just Bita, baby.
Yeah, I know, I know, but the situation with Christine and also with Paige, I think, it's like, you know,
and other people, Bita is like, take a side, it's a him or me.
And it's like and they chose now they've never they've never they've never said anything like that to me
I just it's just I love I love yours and Alex's new friendship, right? Like I think it's cool
But at the same time, I mean and Alex I'm gonna ask you who's trying to kill you girl
Who isn't but let me give you a list right now, buddy
I can tell you not anybody that's in the circle. I talked to not be done not Christine not any of those people
She shouldn't have said okay. That's number one. He does not try to kill you girl
Come on. You can't be that like come on you from the IB2 crowd like you've got tougher skin than that, right?
I'll just leave I'll leave it at that. No, I'm having a conversation. I'm having a conversation. What don't we?
I'll tell Summer like what?
So no, I'm asking Alex something though. I can have conversations with both. I want to have conversations with both you all
I actually like you Alex. I thought you're I think your context is pretty cool
It's like, you know, I fuck with you. I've been really busy the last you know with or so and so there's obviously a lot of myths but
You know, I mean
Tell her what was said Alex. Sure. And then I don't make sure I repeat some of the things you've said throughout the time, psyche. A lot of people say stupid shit sometimes. So, but go ahead, Alex.
All right. When it comes to beta, my best bet is just to let it be. I'm not going to say anything else to her and I have a feeling she won't say anything else to me. So I'm going to leave it at that.
Okay, and that's cool, but if you've got if you've got if you're telling people that you think someone's gonna kill you
That's not really letting it be right though
Well, is it okay to say you what she said what she say Alex, please tell me
He let people know that
Clumsy would be willing to do something to me on her behalf and he declined
Really and you do know that her and clumsy have been kind of going through it right and you really think that clumsy or anyone on this
I mean like come on Alex. You've been around in the savvy to crowd for a while. I
Had and that's why I have to take certain things seriously
But I well in that most people that feel like their lives in danger is not panel hop and telling people that they're someone's trying to kill them
I haven't panel thing that what I've said is what I said on my own panel on my own
Platforms, and that's why I'm letting it be where it is right now. I don't want to talk about beta
Well, but I got questions because when people are saying that somebody's trying to kill them
I'm going to ask I'm asking that's why I'm up here. See cuz unlike other people. I'm gonna continue and you're not letting me
You're not letting you're not letting me I am and you well
I was and I let you talk just now and now I'm responding to what you said
If I have a question to anybody, there's not a motherfucker walking this earth that I am gonna put a shake in my tail feather at all
Right, I'm gonna come to you like a woman and say and psyche you know me
I love you to death me and you I'm gonna come to you and be like like he was up. You know this about me
I don't I don't do the whole jumping from panel panel having conversations and I could do it on my channel too
But why when you're both here and I can have a conversation because one minute everybody's cool. You're on beta's panel
Everybody's look at having a great time and now the same people psyche. It seems like and this is just for my outsider. Okay
Everybody's had beef people have said stupid shit. You've said stupid shit psyche. We all know this right plenty of times
Even before the panel's got the way it got the way it is now
We begged you please like you're so talented. Please focus. Please focus. Please focus. Whatever. Yeah, we are
Yeah, I'm drinking a lot less.
And here we are, right?
Yeah.
What'd you say?
I said I've been drinking a lot less.
And I said, yeah, when I was drinking too much,
I would stop drinking for exactly everything I've tried.
And I see a huge improvement.
And like I've told you, whether you crash out
or you don't crash out, where am I always?
Right here supporting you, right?
And so was Paige and so was Christine and so was beta and it's like now we have this you know new relationship
Which hey, I think it's great
I think you two do a cool little show together and stuff and I think that's great
But I mean like what so page don't matter Tracy. Don't matter. I think don't matter
Be the don't matter. Let me just say so
No, it's like hold on one second. One second. It's like, you know, I'll let you know what it is Alex
You don't have to whisper it under your breath
I will tell you exactly what it is with you. I don't understand why you're going around telling people somebody's trying to kill you
When you're poking you like you're playing and poking the bear, too
Okay
I'm having a conversation. Don't be condescending or pessimistic either. I know big words too, sweetie
But when it comes to like, when I had a little like,
you and I had like a little,
like we're fine on the phone, we're fine on a one,
but when I go on her show, I get attacked.
And it's like, I know people get attacked on this show
and all this kind of stuff,
but I mean, I'm like pretty viciously I was attacked.
And where it's like, and then, so anyway,
since I had like a little, we had a little falling out.
And she would say, I'm thinking so much about her and I wasn't anything vicious or anything
out of my part.
But since then, she hasn't been here.
She just hasn't been here once.
She just disappeared.
I mean, she had a problem at all.
I mean, recently, specifically, other than like, you know.
And then also Paige was gone for a couple of weeks and then Paige just showed up the other
day, came in here and she's like, hi.
And she's like, yeah, I'll come back.
I'm going to come on your show.
And then she never came and then I found out like she went to Bita's show, I was on Bita's and then I heard all the drama and Bita probably was like, don't go over, I don't know, so she hasn't been here either.
But you're assuming because Paige, no, she didn't tell Paige that. Paige, you know, was going through her own, and I just want, EJ Electro, no one's jealous because that means me, Paige, all of us are, Bita, all of us are jealous, we're not jealous.
So, me and you don't have to get along, but stop making assumptions because that's not what it is.
Instead of talking behind people's back. I'm coming up on panel and I'm having a conversation like grown-ups should
But you know just because somebody's psyche and we you know just because people you know page is going through things you know that
I haven't been around because I've been really super busy right just because we're not around doesn't mean we don't support you
came back the other night and she's like oh hi and she was all excited to see me and she's like
yeah and she's like i'm just driving home i'll come on i'll come on the show when i get home
and she never did and then that's like that's pretty and then she went and hung out at betas
and then she probably went and got busy you you automatically assume we're your friend psyche
we've been here for you through thick and thin
We're gonna be here and if Alex comes along that's great too more friends the fuck a Marrior dude
We should all support each other. That's the point just because somebody's not around and I promise you ain't nobody telling nobody picks eyes
Not like that
She's never told me that she's never told me that she's never told Christine that she's never told Paige that
Well, she'll clumsy that and then
Because comes and plays games too
Know yeah, I'm not gonna feel sorry for people that poke the bear until you know what I mean
Just to get some shit going and then they go oh my god. I don't think we're fucking with me
You know I mean
Like if clumsy wasn't doing shit, then okay, but clumsy does his own share of shit, too. We all know that
But yeah, there was some she did say some stuff that she's like now I'm not really remembering
Like how many times has that happened with you though psyche?
How many times have you left me and Paige on the panel and you've gotten drunk and you, you know,
said some shit or let Alex and them say, not you, Alex, I'm talking about a different Alex,
you know, like tell us, suck our dick for us to suck their dicks and all this other stuff.
And it's like, you don't stop them from doing that. But then you want all of us to police our
panels. If somebody says, Oh, you know, I'm pissed off at psyche. But yeah, you let men sit up here
because you are all very good at defending yourselves and like I've accepted me for it.
Okay, so then we can say the same thing to you, then what's wrong with us saying that
same exact thing to you?
That you're a big man and you can defend yourself
So why should we fight everybody that comes on our panels and says something because if you're you understand if you're not gonna kill these guys
Don't talk to women like that
Like that
And it's like, if she comes here, like 90% of the people will be nice, 10% of people might be horrible.
But when I go over there, it's like 90% of the people are horrible to me, and maybe 10% are like, nice.
And then it's like, she doesn't look in my back.
So that's our fault, people don't like you?
Oh my god, it's tons of my former mods and like sweepy and like, you know all over jabroni and 2020
But my point being as a crew as a me as a panel right me as a panel house now
Most people from the sector doesn't come to my panels because I do different type of shit, right?
And I'm fine with that. I'm cool with that
I mean, I've met some cool people up like some people over here and then you know
There's some of us that are never going along and that's fine, too
But so just hypothetically on my panel, right? So you would want me
To if somebody came up and said a bunch of crazy shit, which I do stop that shit on my panel and you know that
I don't allow that kind of any stupid shit like I it's very rare shit
But I like that's why most people don't come to my panels because I don't allow a lot of shit, right?
But then when we're sitting but when we're sitting up here and if Alex or whoever decides to come up and again
Alex not talking about you
And says all the crazy shit that they say and you look at us and you and you say well you guys are tough ass bitches
You can handle it
But if we say that to you then we're in the wrong and and and we don't like you no more. That's not fair psyche
If you expect me to do something, I expect the same respect so if I could you come to my panel and somebody says something crazy to you and I stop that when I come to your panel whether I can find whether I'm a bad bitch you can handle my own or not you as a creator should give me that same respect right or wrong.
Right, and I've been trying to do that better, and I've been trying to enforce the rules
better, and I've had the rules, and everything, like, you know, be respectful to other guests,
and like, sometimes that doesn't work out that way, and it's like, you know, and I understand
like, you know.
And do I get mad at not coming back when it doesn't work out?
Am I, do I, do I still come back and support you no matter what?
Yeah, I can come back, but like, the thing with Christine, like, it was like, I wasn't
trying to like...
Lander Christina
But you were Egan Crystal on you know, I mean she caught her a PDF file and she was saying she was trafficking kids
You know that's that we do anti we do anti trafficking work
She said on this panel and said this about Christine and you were like, oh really? Yeah. Okay, but then you
Watch the clips I was disagreeing with it
You played it a hundred times
I said, I need Christina up here on the panel to talk to, to, to, like,
She's been sick. She's had a grandbaby that's been sick and she's been busy.
Um, so we don't have, we don't sit on panels 24 seven, but when we seen it,
then she came up and you put her in the back.
You let Christina sit up here for 45 minutes and talk crazy about Christine.
And Christine is one of the sweetest people out of all of us.
I know she is, but she was telling me, fuck me and go to hell at the time.
And so then I took her back.
Sit up here and this woman is a professional. This woman does support you and everything and you let this fucking drunk autistic bitch
Sit up here and call her a peanut file. Call her a trafficker
Call her all kinds of shit, and you know, that's the work we do against so really psyche
No, no, that's how play the clip right now play it right now
Play right now
I'm gonna play the clip where Christine was, where Christine was actually talking.
Play the clip where Crystal-Marie is sitting, the reason why Christine got upset.
Okay, because she's not upset for no reason and psyche she loved you and cared about you
And was here with you every day, and you let a truck talk to her like that, and she wasn't even here
Alex let me ask you a question all bullshit aside Alex if you were sitting and you were handling because you're a busy woman too
You're not always on fucking YouTube. I see that about you. We have some substance about you, right?
If you're you're doing your thing right and say you're failed it's fighting an anti-human trafficking, right?
Say even for Schutzen-Gill you're a trafficking survivor like I am and you fight an anti-human trafficking and your and me and you are cool
Right me and you are for real good for like real good associates on this motherfucker
And a girl comes back to Crystal just to be clear. Yes, Crystal Murray 100%
Yes, ma'am. Yes ma'am. Do you know how I feel about Crystal Murray because I do, but I just want a little logic to inspire
Be right. So I'm not crazy for thinking and great for being upset because he let
Sit up here for a while and talk to us about that
Go ahead. But what I would say is that being that people are very aware of the issues
The reason I don't
Say anything else about Crystal Murray's because I'm very aware of her issues, but 100% and I agree with that
He wants people
He wants people to sit here and go to war with people when they go on other panels and say something.
Here's the question. Just suspending reality.
Alex is saying it. Alex is saying the clip. We don't need to watch it. I didn't know if she's saying it or not.
We don't need to watch it. We can talk
Do you think that he was showing that she has issues opposed to trying to get people to turn on Christmas now?
I'm gonna use your work. I'm gonna use your house. What do you I'm gonna use what you just said, right?
We all know she's got issues so to sit here and let this drunk
Talk about a woman that is in nerf the nursing field that fights and all that against this all the kind of stuff
And you just sit up there. We all know so what's the point now?
Don't talk so much about what Christine does because we don't want to put Christine in danger.
So let's not talk about...
I got this. Listen, we're good on that. So I will talk about...
We always talk about the stuff that we do. So first of all, off of that, okay?
Because Christine's actually a part of my shift and that's what we do, right?
So that's no...
You don't get to tell me...
You're not going to put me in danger. What's that?
No, we're not what we're not gonna do is what put Christine in danger if anything was him sitting here letting
Crystal sit here and talk about her being a trafficker, and she's kidnapping kids
That is what put Christine in danger not what we're talking about
I just woke up
Look up a coffee
About the bleach
This is not the video I'm talking about
This is not the video that I am talking about I'm talking about the video with you and her
We just tolerate her because you have her around
There's a difference of tolerating somebody and then sitting there let them calling people and saying that they're kidnapping children
He was in the white that white spurs a game that did hurt me that was trying to kill me
I guess she's like a lot of criminal record and she's trying to cover it up
I'm just gonna break it.
Grab that Christine that we found.
I don't know that Christine that we all know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. She's got a big criminal record.
She's about to get fucked.
What does she do?
She kills kids.
Oh my god.
Who's so... No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's putting somebody in danger.
That's gonna be okay.
And you know like that first thing I told you these people like that to fucking I told you like that the same people or
You believe that their age, you know what I mean? It's like
Your picture you look like Howard Stern right there
I wouldn't
Understand that a bitch
It would act like that like that is like I guess she she's like a lot of criminal record
And she's trying to cover it up. So
We're just gonna break it
And the thing is she didn't mention her name yet you mentioned her name
No, no, no. Yep. I said no. Why what you do? She's a sick Camille. Yeah, she's a bad criminal
But she do
He kills kids. Oh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, you have kicked people off panel for less, but this here she still says
They put them in they put them in these sex trafficking rings and her brother and her friend probably fucking
And we're friends made by the way so and you do that likey
Yeah, they're not trying to help people. They're trying to get people fucking caught up
That's it
Yeah
Why do you think that she says that she's a part that she works for
Fucking
She says
That she is
What's it called, you know first aid what do you
And she also says that she's first line security.
Yeah, she said she's just security guard at the mall the weekend, right?
No.
Okay.
Yeah, she said that, or is that what she told you?
Yeah.
She said she works with Alex at the mall.
False security
But yeah, so she's she's falsing security so she can
Do other bad things with other parts of law. So yeah, she's fucked
Can we pause here?
Yeah, can we eat we can pause it.
Hopefully listen to him.
And Black Archie, you're right.
Words don't matter, but the reason why the words matter
is because Psyche is pissed off at everybody else
because people say stuff to him,
but yet he won't give his supporters the same respect.
So you want us to fight your battles,
but here's this drunk bitch up here saying all this crazy shit dude.
Not cool. Sorry go ahead. I didn't hear her reveal herself because it's like I think we all know who her summary is psyche
You did it for content stop playing
Well, just be honest
I wouldn't be mad if you just be honest.
Stand on what the fuck you're doing.
And I'm cool with that.
I thought I was kind of amused
because it was so ridiculous.
Thank you.
So you did it for content.
Thank you for finally admitting that.
Go ahead, Alex.
I never doubt.
Well, what I was going to say, I've spoken,
Crystal Marie says that we've been friends for five years.
That is not true.
I've only spoken with her extensively.
Maybe it's been a few times at least,
I'd say at least 10 times. What I will say about Crystal is that I can't talk to her anymore, but I'm not excusing her, but she's gone through some stuff and I think sometimes when she drinks or when whatever it is that she's doing, she's reliving things and then.
applying it in fanciful means to who she sees on the live stream.
I think that is what happened that night.
I don't know Christine.
I don't know anything about Christine.
I do think Christine is a very good person
from everything that I've heard about her.
But I think that if anything,
this makes Christine in a positive light opposed to negative because
Part of the reason I did disconnect from certain people around Crystal
is because I saw that they were exploiting the issues that she embodies.
I pulled every single positive and negative video I've ever done on Crystal
because when I realized that there were certain things within Crystal
I just knew, and I hope that one day Crystal is okay, but Crystal has been through these things,
and I think that when she gets upset, and when she's saying these things, she's reliving whatever may have happened to her when she was a young girl.
And I can and I can understand and I can understand and for me to be honest with you crystal
It's I mean at first I was like who the fuck is this broad, you know what I mean?
But after a while, I'm like, okay, it's crystal. This is what crystal does a lot of you probably have some trauma probably
That's not for me in all honesty and all honesty, and I want to make this very clear. It's not about
And for Christine, it might be because it's Christine, right?
But for me, it's not really so much what Crystal says,
because Crystal is going to be Crystal.
It's just what it is, whether she has trauma,
whether it's lived experience, she's fighting through,
or she's just being drunk and saying, silly shit, OK?
Crystal's going to do Crystal.
The issue that I have, and I want to make this very clear,
It's Psyche's whole reason for being upset with some of his main supporters, right?
Is because he feels that when we're other places, people say shit and we don't fight his battles.
But yet when we're sitting here on panel or we're not here,
he uses that same style of stuff that is going on in other places for content.
So I don't have an issue with it, but don't get mad at people about the same shit that you're getting mad about
And then when people get upset about it, hold on one second. Let me finish on my promise to psyche. I'll let you have it
That's the only thing and that's what I want to make very clear
You're upset with a lot of people that are your core fucking supporters because one they're going through shit and haven't been around
Two when they come over here. They don't want to hear guys constantly. No disrespect
But the last time Otto was on on fucking panel. I
Dude, that's all he did summer summer summer summer summer summer summer
I mean just all kinds of weird shit, and it was content for you. I get it. So I bounce you understand don't get mad
Don't get mad at beta. Don't get mad at Christine. Don't get mad at me. Don't get mad at page. Don't get mad at whoever
For doing the same thing that you're doing is making content off of all of us
It's like, you're providing content by coming on the show, okay?
This is supposed to be 100 percent, but you're not, but you're not.
And that's why I don't mind coming up psyche.
How many times you come up here and you say psyche summer, come up here.
Handle all this because these motherfuckers are driving me crazy.
I have no issue doing that.
I have no issue being content.
You're not hearing the issue.
The issue is your bitching and your feelings are hurt
because the same shit is happening on other panels is that is happening here.
Either don't allow it here and then people will do the same for you or hey, baby. It's content. Don't get mad
We all make content is when I see my mods and other chats and my mods
It doesn't matter they're they're respond mother your responsibility when they're here for your channel
They didn't just start saying that psyche and you know that you know you're acting like people are just starting to sit here
And say this just because there are so many reasons why you did use us for content
How many refunds did you have to give to people because you brought Alex back when people would send Alex away or whoever for that matter
Really because I do believe you are we're having to give Christine some and somebody else
Oh, one there was a couple times you had got into it with people with that shit
My point is you don't want to take responsibility for the issues that you've created then you want to put it on us
Summer you always and let me tell you something your mods listen. No, no your mods are not paid
They're not anything your mods are only responsible when they're here at your chat to protect your chat
They're regular people when they go anywhere else. You got to stop that psyche summer
It's not a good look when my own mods are badmouthing me and other chats, okay?
Because you know, I know that first time P-man's gotten frustrated and she's tried to talk to you and you've not a paid not listen to what she said
No, no, no, not everybody goes private because you know what something about this YouTube Street
I don't do private with people because that's when the fucking rule done. That's why I have this shit
I don't even know what's going on because I'm not doing discourse. I'm not doing back behind the scene fucking calls
What every single person nope not doing it
If you can embarrass me in public, you can have a conversation with me in public.
I'm not saying you are.
I'm not psyche.
I'm saying in general.
If something happens on this panel, then we can work it out on this panel.
I don't know, but it's like, the other panels, I have, I kind of not.
So who cares about the other panels?
Fuck it.
Make your content.
I thought I was, you know, I was welcome there and if they didn't think I turned on, I wasn't.
You are, but you got to deal with just like how, okay, psyche, listen, we all know I'm
a loudmouth, right? We all know that I talk my shit and I do what I do, right? So that means
sometimes say I might go and I'm just going to use Alex, for example, that obviously she's
to probably not even do on panels like this, right? But I'm just to use it because she's up here.
If I went to, if I went to Alex's panel and there's people there that I've done
It's not Alex's responsibility to fight my fuck-a-battle.
Those are consequences of my actions
of how I carry myself when I'm out on these YouTube streets.
As a guess, on her un-
And the same thing goes for you.
You talk about how Vita gets drunk
and says stuff,
Psyche, so do you.
I don't anymore.
I haven't-
Well, I'm okay.
I mean, maybe not as much.
I wouldn't say anymore.
I would just say not as much.
Well, I mean it's like well, what am I saying really? I mean I don't understand what I'm saying. It's so bad
You but the same way beta forgets everything you forget everything too because thank you
This ain't the first time that we've had these conversations, right? I've known you for a shit
I'm going on a ficking up. We're not quite a year, but almost a year and
This is not the first time we've had this conversation
And I'm still here and guess what I'm not going anywhere because I fucking love you dude
I'm getting whether you get mad or frustrated at me or not. I'm not I don't walk away, and I'm not giving up on you
But just because I come have hard conversations doesn't mean I don't give a fuck
It actually means I give a shit because I'm not bad-mouthing you anywhere. I'm coming to you and talking to you
No, I didn't order it. I'm sorry
What oh
Door-dash guy delivering for a Lisa Jordana at the door, so
I've told you what to do when you call those places and tell them that you are not ordering any pizza
Please don't send anything because you know people are stupid. That's what they do
And trust me I've had it happen to me if you just call them and tell them listen
I've not I'm not gonna be ordering any pizza today
I mean get any orders don't deliver the eight bags of furlough. I
Minors I were left with my doorstep the other day, but sweetie how many times did we beg you?
Asked you and begged you and said psyche. We believe in your tarot card stuff. We believe in you
We believe in what you're doing. No, I want I be too. No, I want to be like
Howard start no summer no page no beta. No, no, no, don't tell me how to run my show now
This is the consequences from that crowd
Summer, first of all, I told you it's like I had a different idea of IP2.
I had the idea of IP2 as the IP2 streamers.
I didn't know it was just like the fucking IP2 is dead, basically,
and it's all the audience is just torturing looking at everyone as a local.
IP2 always depends.
It's always been the fucking people in the comments that's doing all the stupid shit.
Right, I mean, yeah, but it's like
I started on Benny Blanco and then I was I was on Saints and
And so I do have a gift for tarot reading you are you
Hey, then don't complain when it happens then you can't have it both of you either go and deal with it or you're not
Well, I'm not
Okay. Actually, what Summer just said was, because I've only recently known Psyche, but
what Summer just said resonated with something else that has happened when it's come to another
streamer that I've worked with to where I grew their channel a little bit. I'm actually
at fault and I'll take responsibility. It's possible and I'm not putting words in your
Because I created some websites that have to do with IP2, a lot of people think that IP2 is more than it is simply because of me.
It's the truth.
And part of the reason that I made the websites that I did when it came to IP2, because when I first learned about IP2 and we're talking legitimately about five years ago, I didn't know what it was.
When I learned what it was, I was like, fuck this shit. I'm going to shift it a little bit and I did through some things that I've done over the years.
but it's created a bit of
misconstruism to where some people think
that IP2 is more than it is,
simply because I did some things that,
I'm glad I did some things.
But right now, I mean,
from everything that you just said, Summer.
It sounds to me like Scythe has expressed, okay, I want to grow more, so he's growing more, but as he's growing more, some people that are not compatible with what he's doing.
They are getting upset. I don't know if it's no that's not
I'm sorry, but I have to stop you there because you're just now coming in this this part
And there's a lot of history here and these people aren't upset because he's wanting to grow
We these are the same people that begged him to grow understand that so I have to stop you there because you're making a lot of assumptions
That I'm sorry you're wrong
Okay
I'm talking about a core full of people page beta me Christine a couple other fucking people
You know I mean we have always wanted to see psyche grow always and long before you came around sweetie
And again no disrespect, but you just got here and I don't know who you are and I get your big deal in your your area
The field, but I don't know
You, well, I mean, you just talking about what you did for IB2 and what you invented and all that,
I don't know you, okay? That's where I'm getting at. And so I'm going to talk to you just like I'm
going to talk to anybody else. And you're wrong on that. Bita's not, ain't nobody upset because
he wants to grow. You know how many nights that he was so in-coordinary and he didn't even know
what the fuck was going on and us girls sat on this fucking panel to make sure he stayed alive?
So don't sit there and tell that don't ever put the words of people are not or basically, you know
Don't want to see him grow into it because that is not it. We actually give a fuck about psyche and we didn't just pop in
So give us the respect that we deserve
Like people like leaving me it's like not me like
Like being mad at people or anything like that
It's like people get always get mad at me and then like I'm not then it's like I'm always like
Oh, like don't talk to him and it's like and then people will just say tag me. It's like
We love you to death dude
We get frustrated and we have that right and you act like that, you know
You everybody must have I'll be always gets drunk and this and this like you do the same shit
And you know what we still love you and support you just cuz we're telling you shit that you may not want to hear
Does not mean we don't want to see you grow
Yeah, but it's like not necessarily there's a time of place to like to say these things
And it's not necessarily in front of my whole audience. Hello. It's a time and place when you say it and do it to us in front
Of your whole audience you damn right. I'm gonna jump up here and have a conversation. I don't give a shit
What is that?
Sorry wrong wrong chick on the wrong day because you think I'm not gonna you you you've done this stuff to us in front of everybody
You've allowed things to happen from certain people that have came up here to us in front of everybody
But I'm supposed to have this conversation behind the scenes. No
Summer summer you're not you weren't able to stand up to auto like you did it
You really needed me to like get in the middle of that you were do you really need me to say me?
Okay, so you need me and be to stand up for you, and you can't control what who attacked you
I'll ask you the same fucking question
So you can't you can't handle when art when black RG says something to you don't like
Or when, or with somebody else that you don't like?
I haven't done it for like a long time,
you can't go home.
But no, you just asked me, I can handle honor, right?
And you say, I'm right, I can.
Do I need you to fight my battle?
No, I don't.
But my point being is, what's good for the gender
is good for the goose, baby.
These arguments are you're making are like, you're like.
I'm having a conversation.
I'm not arguing with you.
Okay, boy, but it's like some of these things are like not really as big as a deal
It's like it seems like they're being made okay, but it's a big deal though when it's you though
It's not a big deal when it's me or Christine or beta or page, but it's a big deal when it's you
Oh, well Arthur said this back in like March, you know something for Arthur said second March
And I think that's still the argument today of like why I can't ever be defense like so it's like and I understand
page because she went over she said hey i'll be back and she didn't come back
i'm not a south page you were just crying about that five minutes ago
i'm not crying about anything what i said about page was like page
came back she said from her trip whatever she was real excited to see me she came
right to us you sit there and assume being a toddler not to come over here you would know
she was mad at you and they know one of those things are true what am i supposed to think
You really think that your friend is going through some things you know in her she is going through things in her personal life
You shouldn't assume that being a totter not to come over here. You shouldn't assume. She's mad at you
You should call her and see how she's doing if that's the case, but you assume like everybody else right psyche
It's okay for you to do it, but when we do it, it's wrong right the fuck out of here with that
You're doing the same if you're doing the exact same thing that I'm doing right, which is nothing right
Then it's like why are you with you and you don't like it?
Well, you don't like it either, right?
That's why I'm up here talking to my friend because that's what friends do when they don't like something. They have a conversation
Okay
Yes, you I don't know Alex no disrespect girl, but I don't know her
I'm here for you
Yeah, I mean Alex if we are if me and Alex are gonna get to know each other
We will get to know each other. I don't need you to tell me about Alex or any fucking body else
I want to get to know Alex by damn cell
Not nobody else
But I'm here talking to you
I'm poor time and love and energy into you psyche
Okay, it's a million third parties somewhere. It's like, everyone gets involved and that's what everyone all...
It's like, outside people always mess things up. I always said, if we stand together, like, you know, people stand together,
it's like, you're strong, but it's like, as soon as they say...
Then don't make assumptions just because somebody doesn't come back that they're mad at you, psyche!
Well, let me ask you a question, Psyche, you know I haven't been really been around, right?
Did you come over to any of my lives where I'm crying and all this other stuff that I've
been doing because I had four friends killed this week?
Did you once come over to my fucking live and say, hey Summer, are you okay?
No, I didn't hear about it.
I didn't hear anything about it.
Okay, but you would have heard about it if you came to my live and you see me crying
all week because that's all I did.
And Alex, but all your friends are supposed to come here and check on you, right?
Well, it's like this is where I am
And I'm going to even with me going through shit because I didn't even realize shit was going on until last night
I heard oh people think beat us for gonna fucking try to kill people and all this weird shit
I'm like what the fuck is going on? That's why I'm up here. Yeah. Well, you know, I got outreach tonight
But that's my point being is like I ain't been around for a week and a half because I have four friends killed
Okay, I'm sorry, but did you come check on me? I'm sorry. I didn't I didn't know that and I apologize
You know and I haven't I have you know
I haven't been pretty self-absorbed and not like just in my own chat and like not
I'm asking for a baby is there's a lot of people that care about you psyche and
Even with all the shit we got going on even with everything I got going on. I'm still over here like dude you cool you straight
Yeah, and I'm not really give me the same respect
I'm trying to I'm not really cool because it's like people keep getting mad at me and it's like I'm not mad at anybody
I'm not really mad at anybody. We're not mad at you. We're mad at your hypocrisy
You want us to fight your battles, but you don't want to give the same return you want us to check up on you
But you don't do the same
Whoever's petting your tail feather in that moment, making you feel good, that's who you check on.
And right now, and this is not me being jealous, but right now, it's Alec.
So all of us don't matter.
And this is not a jealousy thing, this is a reality thing.
Because I could never be jealous of Alec, because she is a woman,
and I hope she does thrives and does every fucking thing she's supposed to.
I'm not one of those petty bitches, that is not what this is about.
But that's how you do things, Psyche.
This is a cycle.
Yeah, but you don't see you're very heavily criticizing me in front of my entire audience in front of everybody
I'm talking to my friend
But why does it have to be in front of every
Disrespect this in front of everybody
Disrespect in front of everybody. That's how I like you
Yeah, and you are yelling somewhere. It's like, that's what causes me to yell, right?
And it's like, you know I'm deaf in one of my ears. I talk loud. You know when I'm yelling, this is me talking.
So don't use that because you already know the truth.
Okay, but it's...
I talk loud because I'm deaf in one of my fucking ears.
I feel the negativity very strongly.
No, you feel the frustration and the hurt.
But why would I do that like I just told you you've been so self-consumed that one of your people ain't even been around in a minute
And you didn't even bother to come check on me
I didn't know anything, but you would have if you came and checked on me. I don't check, I mean I'm not going to any place summer because I keep getting attacked in places unless, you know, unless I'm invited.
You're not being attacked on my page, especially my hot mess summer page, so don't even say that, you know that. I don't allow that shit in my chat, especially on my hot mess page. Everyone knows that, that's why happily none of these people come over there.
They know that's my community page, they know I act as stupid over there, you know that.
I don't care what people do, am I your friend Psyche?
Yeah.
Then please, check on me like I check on you.
Okay.
And don't assume everybody's mad at you just because they're not around dude, we got life.
You know when you're driving around and stuff.
If you would have checked in on me, you would have known that I've had a hell of a fucking
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You know, it's like sometimes I don't go go in and they check on people like I should
You go other places you ain't just at your panel. So don't say that either
Because I've been supporting you all on other shit too
Every single time you all go live who shows up even if I'm in there just saying right and hey fuckers because I'm busy
And I just want to give you a click and the support let you know. Hey, I'm here supporting you
Yeah, I know I know and I appreciate you. I appreciate you very much. And it's like and I
Continue you're taking
You're taking criticism and all we're asking is psyche. Give us the same treatment you want from us
Right, okay, but and I will and I'm not gonna ask you to fight any battles for me
And it's like I don't expect you to do it. I don't expect you to and it's like and I will
Either either or don't get mad at anybody else for that either
Yeah, but it's just like be that actually was attacking me though
All the time and I'll give Alex and everybody a piece of advice stay out of it
Because then to go back and forth all the fucking time and they cannot work it out as long as everybody else is thinking
They're fucking nose in it that has nothing to do with it
Don't say silly shit
Yeah
Uncle fucker and everything else dude, so come on let's not play that game you both have said stupid shit and
Everybody else needs to say to fuck out of it. Ain't nobody knows savior
There's history here.
I've never said about anybody that I've had to run their shit.
Well, I'm just letting it be fucking on while I'm here.
Because you two go back and forth all the time
and you both taste some good shit.
How do we have that person, this person, this person,
this person, this person, we'll have this person on the,
like, everyone's telling me how to run their show.
It's like, I know I'm like newer than all of you
and everything.
The show, I'm talking about friendship.
I'm talking about friendship.
You run the show how you want, just don't get mad when other people, and you go other places, say shit, and they don't do nothing.
Because if you're doing the same thing over here, they're just gonna follow suit. That's all.
I'm not telling you how to run your shit. Run your shit however you want. I'm gonna be here regardless.
Summer, I never had a problem on- I never- I've never said I had a problem on your show or anything. It was-
I know what you're having, because I don't allow that shit.
It was I was having problems on being a show because we didn't have a talk
It's something that don't go over being a show
In fact don't go over being a show cool
But all I'm gonna say is anybody that's listening that knows anything that knows anything say the fuck out of that
These two fight like brothers and sisters and they will make up. I promise you
And so I really want I really want things to work out
Oh my god, yeah, he has her fucking tattoo tattooed on his fucking chest. They're gonna make up. They do this
This is what they do
And, uh, I think maybe, like, things got, like, things might have gotten, like, um, like, you know, thrown out of-
Get it out of hand!
Both of you are Oz villains or heart, and everybody else and their fucking mother is in the middle of it instead of just you two.
When people stay the fuck out of it, you all are able to work it out.
Yeah, I mean we're gonna be ever fine talking one-on-one like that's what I noticed
But it's like it's only when other people try to stick their shit in and then it's rouse it back up and both of you
All should be securing your friendship and say fuck what everybody else say cuz trolls are gonna do everything in their place
To tear friendships real friendships apart. I get it. I understand you
Do know I do because I know that's been saying that I was like I was like
Even when Janet and Vita were like, you know, kind of like, you know...
I'm not talking about fucking Janet, dude.
Okay, but I'm saying that people would say,
oh, they're trying to control your show or whatever.
Like, they're gonna tell you what to do, like, blah, blah.
But they would just say that to make me feel, like, you know, insecure or like...
And Jada, don't fuck with Vita alone before I get on your goddamn ass, dude.
Leave her the fuck alone.
She's I told you numerous times to leave her the fuck alone.
Leave her the fuck alone or I'm gonna get on that ass, too.
Stop being a fucking weirdo, dude.
No means no.
Leave her the fuck alone.
God damn you're a fucking man go pick on a fucking man
Little for your act like a little fucking weasel, dude
Think you can get up to my psyches ass because they're them two more beefing and war in the shit stay the fuck out of it
J-Dog and shut the fuck up about her dude
Worry about your goddamn wife
And he's a he's another one that's all in your fucking, you know, that's what he wants to do because he doesn't like beta
So as long as he can get in your ear and get you to still you know what I mean?
It's stupid shit like that and you're better than that psyche and beta damn sure is better than that
Fuck him dude
Being fucking weird J dog
It's like I'm sure the fuck it won't come up and if he wants it he can get it
I do want things I mean, I think I want to pick on this. Oh my gosh. Oh, no, I don't think it's the time right now to talk
I think I don't think it's the time the perfect time like maybe
It actually I was being cool today
I don't think fuck this I am on under the shit
Let's see, here's Grim, let's see, Black Archie, let's see, J-Dog, please open your
penis in your hand, come on Archie, thank you so much.
Anyway, come on up, here we go, okay, so Otto is back, okay?
What's up Otto?
You said you want to talk to Alex?
Me?
Oh, no, yeah, I think it's for ocean Alex or auto
Okay, there he goes utter you there
Hi, I'm here. Did you want to say hi to Alex? Hello?
Hey, oh, I really did say hi to Alexandra. I was just wondering are you okay summer?
I'm perfectly fine Otto. I'm having a discussion with my friend and I would thank you for checking on me
But it's just a friend. It's a conversation between two friends, and I'd like to keep it that way
My condolences I did hear that you lost some people. I'm sorry. Thank you
Hey, what's up psyche how you're healthy going Alex? Hello everybody
What's up today? Why?
Summer I have no beef with you. I have no beef with nobody up here
Why are you saying her name just ignore? You're a man dude ignore it. I know she brought me up. I'm not bringing her up
I'm leaving her alone. Okay. I would like I told
But we got to read all of it summer, please read all of it
Because you you're a man and you could just leave it alone. It's that simple just leave it the fuck alone
Okay, listen, okay, and then second of all, I'm not in psyche's ear. I'm not in nobody's ear
You can see every time I see you somewhere. It's B to B to B to B. So just I'm just saying why can't you just leave it alone?
I won't mention her name anymore. Okay, that would be great. That would be that's done. Okay, I got no
I got no beef with nobody, right
Just getting somewhere I'm just gonna I get you I get you and I know I know you're trying to help summer
I know you're trying to
You know your friend to psyche, you know, but sometimes it can't go a little you know psyche. He don't like to be
How would you say what beta get to him yell at him on it on the live streamer
Okay, okay. Well, that was my mistake, but I'm just saying it was a reference point last part
Because the reference is me. I'm the one talking to him. Okay, but I just think that's what he doesn't like
He doesn't like the yelling. He doesn't like all that
Conversation with my friend and thank you, but we don't need a referee. I appreciate your advice though
No, I'm not a referee at all not a referee at all, but I just came up here to clear the air because I'm not in nobody's ear
I'm strictly just like
Just walk away from it. You're a whole grown-ass fuck a man. There's plenty of men who fight with fucking fuckers antelope
I'm not I'm not gonna mess with nobody anymore as far as females. Thank you. Thank you
That'd be great. That was it. That was it. But Psyche, I'm not in his ear. I love Psyche. He's my homeboy.
I love Alex. Alex is a good person. I have no beef with Otto.
You know, I even got no beef with you. Summer, I like you. Summer, I fucking do.
I think you're awesome fucking woman. You were fucking the shit you hold down.
I see what you hear, community outreach is fucking awesome.
Keep it up, and I'm sorry for your loss this summer,
our legit art.
So I understand your emotions are a little riled up,
especially if things haven't checked up on you.
So I understand, I 100% understand,
but I got no beef and I'm not in no beef here, okay?
All right, I love you guys, peace out.
Tyler.
Alexandra, are you in a wheelchair?
Yes
Okay, yeah, that's that's okay. That's it. It's okay
Well, a lot of people are you not?
No, I'm not
Sorry, I was trying not to know I'm here. I can I can go
I can, I can walk. It's a miracle.
A miracle. Okay.
I'm sorry.
I put hands on her. She can walk. Holler.
Okay, good good. I'm okay. Good psyche. I'm not gonna I gotta get literally I gotta jump off
I gotta get ready for outreach. I love you, dude. Okay, I really do and
The stuff would be to I just hope people say out of it. Let them work their things out
They will work it out if everybody stays out of it like seriously like I mean he has her tattooed on his chest people like come on
But with everybody else taking their fucking hands in the cookie jar
It just gets worse and it gets worse and it gets flared up and it gets flared up
And psyche I promise you people aren't mad people people yeah
People might get frustrated and shit like that because of certain things happening
Which we don't have to read us because we've done talked about it for a good hour probably but you know what I mean like
Just yeah
You what you want?
Just just understand dude like people that have been here with you for a long time and and they're still and look
We just still here. She's in the chat even if she's frustrated and she's whatever she's still here dude
So you've got a core people that have loved you and had your fucking back for a long time and DJ
I don't give a fuck if we get along or not
But I ain't ever shut in the fuck up and you ain't gonna be the bitch to ever do it. So fuck you too, bitch
Anyway, everybody have a great day. Alex. Have a great day. I don't have a great day. I will see y'all later
Holler
Have a good night summer
Okay, RG's here
one second
Hello
It's fun. She dog. I heard it heard. I was in a bag in Iran. He just took right off
It's funny. I that amuses me. Like how was your day today?
Because because I because you're there and you didn't make any
I understand what you're saying auto you're you're saying that I get it
Jump into you know, the I was wrong
It's because you move you weren't making any kind of movement
Sexy with those glasses hiding your fuck me eyes. I see you baby. I see you. Yeah
And when I listen, I really intensely listen, so, yeah.
Yeah.
You were actually turning to summer, and so you were, yeah, you were focused.
You were focused.
So which which led me to believe that you were in a wheelchair
No, I'm no, I'm I'm a pretty active person. I I recently gone to a e-scooter accident from being too active
Yeah, I was I was impressed I gotta say yeah, well, I was an athlete for a very long time
Don't make too many points, Jimman.
Well, we're the best ones actually
Yeah, I was a cheerleader basketball track cross country every tennis every kind of sport
I used to see what right into that's a porn. That's kind of a weird jump
But all right. Oh, I went to school for computer science before I went no kidding. Well a real career, you know
Makes you think how you got here
I'll tell you how I got here
They outsourced our jobs
And I got an H1B Indians. I hear that pre chance. They did the fucking H1B Indians
I hate them all but you know, I got a couple pamphlets for you Alex about the H1B Indians
I'm gonna send them to you. I think you'll you'll you'll get a lot of information
There's only a couple people a couple people that
And that was summer J dog
Both of them stood out for me. Are you homeless auto cool people?
No, I'm not like that brick behind you
Makes me think you're like
I
Know it's a stereotype and I'm not trying to be offensive
No, you're you're you're sorry about volume. It's really turned on Alexander. It is Alexander. Is it mine or his?
I could turn my life
Is that better Alexandra auto? Yes. I'm gonna say it is Alexandra. Yes
Where where where are you from? Where are you from? I?
Was born in Kirkland Washington raised in Texas
Spit a lot of my life in Florida, but I've traveled all over the world. That's my parents are African-American
I know I'm a little bit different. It's okay
Any other questions I'm pretty intrigued by these two I think I'm sensing a love connection
No, what it is is that Otto is used to somebody with my look sounding differently
So he's quantitizing it in his mind. I think there's a connection here. It don't don't you know
I
Think there's a real connection here between auto and alex
I might have I might have outcuted you today psyche don't get mad
Oh God I got a ring. I didn't mean to I didn't mean to see it's like he's gonna kick me because I outcuted him today
Sorry
Any woman but uh, no not necessarily not necessarily I got a new ring not necessarily
What oh you oh you got new ones. Oh
Look at you
So funny like psyche, you know what this means this means that you and I probably have to have a personal relationship
instead of a public friendship because despite everything I took you
From your people a little bit. I'm sorry
You didn't and you really you really didn't like it's like I was like waiting for somebody to like
Come in like I'm still here. I'm still here. It's it's just that
My energy is very
Um potent
Yeah, okay, and you've seen that
So that's what it that's a part of it. That's a part of it. I know it but it's like you know what it's like
You know at the time you came into my life. It was like I was really having a hard time like really really having a hard time
I know that's why I you know and you came in
So breath I just have a very strong. I have a very strong energy and I did not used to always be this way
It's just
it's evolved over time.
We're January 7th babies, you know.
I know, I know, and that's why,
like people don't understand that
because we're January 7th, both, for those who don't know,
psyche and I, we're different birth years.
I'm a couple of years older than psyche.
But there's just-
Alex, are you that full of yourself?
Am I myself?
Asin, are you that full of yourself?
Are you that full of yourself?
yourself. Yes. Oh, I'm so full of myself. It's it's
ridiculous. Okay. I can see because you clearly like as
soon as I jump off panel, you're like, my bad psyche, if I
took you from your people, this is nothing to do with you. I
know you will maybe want it to to think that it has to do with
you, sweetie. It doesn't though. It don't though because you're
no, there's nothing that you found out. There's nothing you
can bring to the table that I can't bring to the table.
Not why I'm not why I'm talking. Have I ever insulted you? That's what I'm trying to do. You kind of just did though actually
You kind of just did that's why I came back up here because
You're gonna I haven't I haven't even gotten to talk to you. You didn't let me talk before when you want to have the conversation
Actually, I did let you talk. I'm talking about what you just said just now. You're like psyche
I'm sorry. We're gonna have a friendship from behind
Everything that's what we have to do. Yes
But why are you why I'm not gonna be
You think this is about you in part impart it is
Though my issue is the psyche has not a goddamn thing do you know what's
You tell us tell us tell us what's in said
Okay, no matter what you're gonna yell at me. That's what I figured. No, I didn't I haven't yelled at you the whole time until I jumped
off panel and he's like I'm taking you away from your friends. How are you taking somebody off there?
No, I'm not yelling. I can't yell at you. I'm not yelling
Me. Oh, no, sweetie. This is not yelling at you. I can though if you would like to feel like you're you're you definitely
I didn't give a fuck about your feelings. I'm not your mother. So that's
So I don't give I shouldn't care about your I'm just gonna let you know I'm just gonna let you know that I think you think you're all
That in a bag of chips, but maybe this shit has nothing to do with I am all of them
Before you we knew him before you and so the issues that we have with him is because of before you how come but
I know him now and that's why I'm we all know him now. We all know him now, baby
Just because you buy him stuff now. We don't know him. I don't know him as long as you've known him
You just okay, so it's not a competition though. That's how you're trying to act like it is
No, it's not but you did because you're giggling like everything I just said up here and was telling him and you're like he
Well, we gotta be friends behind behind the scene because I'm taking you away from your friends
Maybe you ain't got shit that I ain't everybody else ain't got that
Summer if you want to hate me, you have full permission to
That's what you want. Hey, you want somebody to hate you. I don't give two fucks to hate you
I don't hate anybody. It takes a lot of energy to hate people. I like
I actually like you a lot. I don't hate you.
Well, I don't hate you, so I can't remember.
But considering everything that you said that you went through,
I don't want to have the conversation with you
because you're in the midst of something really major.
No, I'm in the midst of having a conversation with my friend
and I jumped off the panel and you thought it was funny
and like, oh, I guess because I'm kind of taking you away from your friend.
We're children. We're not children.
Yes, I did. I don't need you to remind me that I lose people all the time because of the work that I do
I don't need you to remind me that Alex, but it's meant something to you
Yeah, and that has nothing to do with the conversation. We're having right now. It does everything that I can separate the two I
Can't
Well, that's well that that's your problem not mine. I can't it is my problem
I can't and that's why I'm not well. I just want to let you know you're not taking them away from anyone
We're all friends dude. It's not a fucking competition
okay that was a weird statement somebody from your at the way the way you
carry yourself like that when I look at you which I look at you as someone that
carries I know you bother me Alex why would you bother me Alex why would I
we're both from the sex industry we both are beautiful women we both are
educated why the fuck would you bother me you just told me why bother me no I
It wasn't intended to be
Okay, well, I was just letting you know that it was so and you said it's not being a meant to be intended
I don't hate you. I don't I don't know you enough to hate to hate you
I actually had some respect for you because I think you carry yourself a little bit higher, but why would I be?
Anything like it's not competition, baby. We're we me and you on the same fucking playing field
Believe it or not
We're both from an industry and we both turned our life around. No, it's not. No, not everything's because people are more
Or should people tell people I know because in two weeks what I tell you the same shit if you say something like that
With what you've been through do you get how did you become a porn star Alex? What meant what was so traumatic that puts you in the sex industry?
So you want to talk about my problem to talk about yours
I'll say in the back, we don't have to-